Number of Language	80	For Customer Reference Only!
Enum Value	Module Name	Region ID	Description	English	Tr_Chinese	Si_Chinese	Thai	Spanish	French	German	Russian	Italian	Arabic	Portuguese	Turkish	Vietnamese	Indonesian	Malaysian	Hindi	Danish	Czech	Polish	Hungarian	Finnish	Norwegian	Slovak	Dutch	Swedish	Croatian	Romanian	Slovenian	Greek	Hebrew	Bulgarian	Marathi	Persian	Urdu	Tamil	Bengali	Punjabi	Telugu	Ukrainian	Gujarati	Kannada	Zulu	Xhosa	Swahili	Afrikaans	Lithuanian	Latvian	Estonian	Armenian	Georgian	Moldovan	Malayalam	Oriya	Albanian	Assamese	Azerbaijani	Chinese.Cantonese	Catalan	Canadian.French	Icelandic	Latin.Am.Spanish	Macedonian	Brazil. Portuguese	Serbian	Sesotho	Tagalog	UK.English	Hausa	Yoruba	Kazak	Basque	Filipino	Galician	Igbo	Irish	Myanmar	Lao	Khmer	Korea	Zawgyi	
STR_GX_TETRIS_GAME_NAME	GAME	TITLE, ICONTEXT	tetris	Tetris	俄羅斯方塊	俄罗斯方块	Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	Тетрис	Tetris	تتريس	Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	टेट्रिस	Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	טטריס	Тетрис	टेट्रिस	تتریس	ٹیٹریس	டெட்ரிஸ்	টেট্রিস	ਟੈਟ੍ਰਿਸ	టెట్రిస్	Тетріс	ટેટ્રિસ	ಟೆಟ್ರಿಸ್	I-Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	ტეტრისი	Tetris	ടെട്രിസ്	ଟେଟ୍ରିସ୍ |	Tetris	টেট্ৰিছ	Tetris	俄羅斯方塊	Tetris	Tétris	Tetris	Tetris	Тетрис	Tetris	Тетрис	Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	Тетрис	Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	Tetris	តេទ្រីស	테트리스	Tetris	
STR_GX_TETRIS_GRID	GAME	UNLIM	tetris	Grid	網格	格子	ตาราง	Grid	Grille	Raster	Сетка	Griglia	الشبكة	Rede	Grid	Lưới	Grid	Grid	ग्रिड	Gitter	Mřížka	Siatka	Rács	Ruudukko	Rutenett	Mriežka	Raster	Rutnät	Mreža	Grilă	Mreža	Πλέγμα	רֶשֶׁת	Решетка	ग्रिड	شبکه	گرڈ	கட்டம்	গ্রিড	ਗਰਿੱਡ	గ్రిడ్	Сітка	ગ્રીડ	ಗ್ರಿಡ್	Igridi	Igridi	Gridi	Rooster	Tinklelis	Režģis	Võre	Ցանց	ბადე	Grilă	ഗ്രിഡ്	ଗ୍ରୀଡ୍	Rrjeti	গ্ৰিড	Grid	網格	Quadrícula	Grille	Grid	Grid	Решетка	Grade	Грид	Grid	Grid	Grid	Grid	Akoj	Тор	Sarea	Grid	Reixa	Grid	Greille	ဂရစ်	ຕາຂ່າຍໄຟຟ້າ	ក្រឡាចត្រង្គ	그리드	ဂရစ်	
STR_GX_TETRIS_EASY	GAME	TWOSTATE, C150_1	tetris	Easy	簡單	简单	ง่าย	Fácil	Facile	Leicht	Легкий 	Facile	سهل	Fácil	Kolay	Dễ	Mudah	Mudah	आसान	Nem	Jednoduchá	Łatwy	Könnyű	Helppo	Enkelt	Jednoduchá	Gemakkelijk	Nybörjare	Lagano	Uşor	Lahko	Εύκολο	קל	Лесно	सुलभ	ساده	آسان	சுலபம்	সহজ	ਅਸਾਨ	ఈజీ	Легко	સહેલું	ಸುಲಭ	Okulula	Lula	Rahisi	Maklik	Lengvas	Viegla	Lihtne	Հեշտ	იოლი	Uşor	ലളിതം	ସହଜ		সহজ		簡單				Fácil		Fácil				Easy									လွယ်	ງ່າຍ	ងាយ	쉽게	လြယ္ကူေသာ	
STR_GX_TETRIS_NORMAL	GAME	TWOSTATE, C150_1	tetris	Normal	正常	正常	ปกติ	Normal	Normal	Normal	Средний	Normale	عادي	Normal	Normal	Bình thường	Normal	Normal	सामान्य	Normal	Normální	Normalny	Normál	Normaali	Normalt	Normálna	Normaal	Normalt	Normalno	Normal	Normalno	Κανονικό	רגיל	Нормален режим	सर्वसामान्य	معمولى	نارمل	சாதாரணம்	সাধারণ	ਸਧਾਰਨ	నార్మల్	Нормально	સામાન્ય	ಸಾಮಾನ್ಯ	Okujwayelekile	Qhelekile	Kawaida	Normaal	Normalus	Normāla	Tava-	Նորմալ	ნორმალური	Normal	സാധാരണം	ସାମାନ୍ୟ		সাধাৰণ		普通				Normal		Normal				Normal									ပုံမှန်	ທໍາມະດາ	ធម្មតា	일반	ပံုမွန္	
STR_GX_TETRIS_HARD	GAME	TWOSTATE, C150_1	tetris	Hard	困難	困难	ยาก	Difícil	Difficile	Schwer	Сложный 	Difficile	صعب	Difícil	Zor	Khó	Sulit	Sukar	कठोर	Svær	Obtížná	Trudny	Nehéz	Vaikea	Vanskelig	Náročná	Moeilijk	Svårt	Teško	Dificil	Težko	Δύσκολο	קשה	Остри	दुर्लभ	سخت	سخت	கடினம்	কঠিন	ਮੁਸ਼ਕਿਲ	హార్డ్	Складно	કપરું	ಹಾರ್ಡ್ (ಕಷ್ಟ)	Okunzima	Nzima	Ngumu	Moeilik	Sunkus	Grūta	Raske	Բարդ	რთული	Dificil	കഠിനം	କଠିନ		কঠিন		困難				Difícil		Difícil				Hard									ခက်	ຍາກ	ពិបាក	하드	ခက္ေသာ	
STR_GX_TETRIS_HELP_DESCRIPTION	GAME	UNLIM	tetris	(1)There are seven shapes of block, displayed in different colors. \n(2)Initial speed in easy is 0. When score is past 500, the speed will increase a unit. You can enter the next level on 8 or 16 speed. \n(3)5/OK - pause/continue; up - rotate block; left/right - move block left/right;down - move block to the bottom. \n(4)Sound can be on/off. \n(5)Grid on will facilitate you.	(1)方塊有七種形狀，以不同的顏色顯示。 \n(2)簡單關卡初始速度為零。當分數超過500時，速度會增加一個單位。當速度達到8或16時，可以選擇進入下一關。 \n(3)5/OK 將暫停/繼續；向上將旋轉方塊；左/右將向左或向右移動方塊；向下將把方塊移到底部。 \n(4)支援聲音，可以開/關。 \n(5)格紋會方便你，可以開啟/關閉。	(1)方块形状共有7种，以不同颜色显示。\n(2)简单关卡初始速度为零，当分数大于500时，速度会增加一个单位，当速度达到8或16时，可以选择进入下一关。\n(3)5/OK暂停/继续；向上旋转方块；向左/向右移动方块；向下将方块移至最下方。\n(4)支持声音，可开启/关闭。\n(5)网格将为您提供便利，可开启/关闭。	(1) มีบล็อก 7 รูปแบบซึ่งแสดงเป็นสีต่างๆ \n(2) ความเร็วเริ่มต้นในโหมดง่ายคือ 0 เมื่อคะแนนผ่าน 500 แล้ว ความเร็วจะเพิ่มขึ้นหนึ่งหน่วย คุณสามารถเข้าสู่ระดับถัดไปด้วยความเร็ว 8 หรือ 16 \n(3) 5/ตกลง - หยุดชั่วคราว/ดำเนินการต่อ; ขึ้น - หมุนบล็อก; ซ้าย/ขวา - เลื่อนบล็อกไปทางซ้าย/ขวา; ลง - เลื่อนบล็อกไปด้านล่าง \n(4) สามารถเปิด/ปิดเสียงได้ \n(5) การเปิดกริดจะช่วยอำนวยความสะดวกให้กับคุณ	(1) Hay siete formas de bloques, que se muestran en diferentes colores. \n(2) La velocidad inicial en el nivel fácil es 0. Cuando la puntuación supere los 500, la velocidad aumentará una unidad. Puede ingresar al siguiente nivel con una velocidad de 8 o 16. \n(3) 5/OK: pausa/continuar; arriba: rotar el bloque; izquierda/derecha: mover el bloque a la izquierda/derecha; abajo: mover el bloque al fondo. \n(4) El sonido puede activarse o desactivarse. \n(5) La cuadrícula activada lo facilitará.	(1) Il existe sept formes de blocs, affichées dans différentes couleurs. \n(2) La vitesse initiale en mode facile est de 0. Lorsque le score dépasse 500, la vitesse augmente d'une unité. Vous pouvez entrer dans le niveau suivant à une vitesse de 8 ou 16. \n(3) 5/OK - pause/continuer ; haut - faire pivoter le bloc ; gauche/droite - déplacer le bloc; bas - déplacer le bloc vers le bas. \n(4) Le son peut être activé/désactivé. \n(5) La grille activée vous facilitera la tâche.	(1)Es gibt sieben Block, die in unterschiedlichen Farben angezeigt werden. \n(2)Die Anfangsgesch im einfachen Modus ist 0. Wenn die Punktz über 500 liegt, erhöht sich die Geschwindigkeit um eine Einheit. Sie können das nächste Level mit 8 oder 16 Geschwindig erreichen. \n(3)5/OK – Pause/Fortfahren; hoch – Block drehen; links/rechts – Block nach links/rechts bewegen; runter – Block nach unten bewegen. \n(4)Ton kann ein-/ausges werden. \n(5)Das einges Raster erleichtert Ihnen die Arbeit.	(1)Существует семь блоков, которые отображаются разными цветами. \n(2)Начальная скорость в легком режиме — 0. Когда счет превышает 500, скорость увеличивается на одну единицу. Вы можете достичь следующего уровня на 8 или 16 скоростях. \n(3)5/OK — Пауза/Продолжить; вверх — повернуть блок; влево/вправо — переместить блок влево/вправо; вниз — переместить блок вниз. \n(4)Звук можно включить/выключить. \n(5)Сетка на экране упрощает игру.	(1)Ci sono sette blocchi, che sono visualizzati in colori diversi. \n(2)La velocità iniziale in modalità facile è 0. Quando il punteggio supera 500, la velocità aumenta di un'unità. Puoi raggiungere il livello successivo a 8 o 16 velocità. \n(3)5/OK - Pausa/Continua; su - ruota il blocco; sinistra/destra - sposta il blocco a sinistra/destra; giù - sposta il blocco verso il basso. \n(4)Il suono può essere attivato/disattivato. \n(5)La griglia rende il gioco più facile.	(1) هناك سبعة كتل، والتي يتم عرضها بألوان مختلفة. \n(2) سرعة البدء في الوضع السهل هي 0. عندما تكون النتيجة أكثر من 500، تزداد السرعة بوحدة واحدة. يمكنك الوصول إلى المستوى التالي عند 8 أو 16 سرعة. \n(3) 5/موافق - إيقاف مؤقت/متابعة؛ لأعلى - تدوير الكتلة؛ لليسار/لليمين - تحريك الكتلة لليسار/لليمين؛ لأسفل - تحريك الكتلة لأسفل. \n(4) يمكن تشغيل/إيقاف الصوت. \n(5) تجعل الشبكة اللعب أسهل.	(1)Existem sete blocos, apresentados em cores diferentes. \n(2)A velocidade inicial no modo fácil é 0. Quando a pontuação ultrapassa os 500, a velocidade aumenta uma unidade. Pode alcançar o próximo nível a 8 ou 16 velocidades. \n(3)5/OK - Pausa/Continuar; para cima - rode o bloco; esquerda/direita - desloca o bloco para a esquerda/direita; para baixo - mova o bloco para baixo. \n(4)O som pode ser ligado/desligado. \n(5)A grelha facilita o jogo.	(1)Farklı renklerde gösterilen yedi blok vardır. \n(2)Kolay modda başlangıç ​​hızı 0'dır. Puan 500'ün üzerinde olduğunda hız bir birim artar. 8 veya 16 hızda bir sonraki seviyeye ulaşabilirsin. \n(3)5/OK - Duraklat/Devam et; yukarı - bloğu döndür; sola/sağa - bloğu sola/sağa hareket ettir; aşağı - bloğu aşağı hareket ettir. \n(4)Ses açılıp kapatılabilir. \n(5)Açık ızgara oyunu kolaylaştırır.	(1)Có bảy khối, được hiển thị bằng các màu khác nhau. \n(2)Tốc độ bắt đầu ở chế độ dễ là 0. Khi điểm trên 500, tốc độ tăng thêm một đơn vị. Bạn có thể đạt đến cấp độ tiếp theo ở 8 hoặc 16 tốc độ. \n(3)5/OK - Tạm dừng/Tiếp tục; lên - xoay khối; trái/phải - di chuyển khối sang trái/phải; xuống - di chuyển khối xuống. \n(4)Có thể bật/tắt âm thanh. \n(5)Lưới trên giúp chơi dễ hơn.	(1) Ada tujuh blok, yang ditampilkan dalam warna yang berbeda. \n(2) Kecepatan awal dalam mode mudah adalah 0. Ketika skor lebih dari 500, kecepatan meningkat satu unit. Anda dapat mencapai level berikutnya pada 8 atau 16 kecepatan. \n(3) 5/OK - Jeda/Lanjutkan; atas - putar blok; kiri/kanan - gerakkan blok ke kiri/kanan; bawah - gerakkan blok ke bawah. \n(4) Suara dapat dinyalakan/dimatikan. \n(5) Kisi-kisi yang aktif membuat permainan lebih mudah.	(1) Terdapat tujuh blok, yang dipaparkan dalam warna yang berbeza. \n(2)Kelajuan permulaan dalam mod mudah ialah 0. Apabila markah melebihi 500, kelajuan meningkat sebanyak satu unit. Anda boleh mencapai tahap seterusnya pada 8 atau 16 kelajuan. \n(3)5/OK - Jeda/Teruskan; ke atas - putar blok; kiri/kanan - alihkan blok ke kiri/kanan; turun - gerakkan blok ke bawah. \n(4)Bunyi boleh dihidupkan/dimatikan. \n(5)Grid dihidupkan menjadikan permainan lebih mudah.	(1) सात ब्लॉक हैं, जो अलग-अलग रंगों में प्रदर्शित होते हैं। \n(2) आसान मोड में शुरुआती गति 0 है। जब स्कोर 500 से अधिक होता है, तो गति एक इकाई बढ़ जाती है। आप 8 या 16 गति पर अगले स्तर तक पहुँच सकते हैं। \n(3) 5/OK - रोकें/जारी रखें; ऊपर - ब्लॉक घुमाएँ; बाएँ/दाएँ - ब्लॉक को बाएँ/दाएँ घुमाएँ; नीचे - ब्लॉक को नीचे घुमाएँ। \n(4) ध्वनि को चालू/बंद किया जा सकता है। \n(5) ग्रिड चालू होने से खेल आसान हो जाता है।	(1) Der er syv blokke, som vises i forskellige farver. \n(2)Starthastigheden i let tilstand er 0. Når scoren er over 500, øges hastigheden med en enhed. Du kan nå det næste niveau ved 8 eller 16 hastigheder. \n(3)5/OK - Pause/Fortsæt; op - roter blok; venstre/højre - flyt blok til venstre/højre; ned - flyt blokken ned. \n(4)Lyd kan slås til/fra. \n(5)Gitteret på gør spillet lettere.	(1) Existuje sedm bloků, které jsou zobrazeny v různých barvách. \n(2)Počáteční rychlost ve snadném režimu je 0. Když je skóre vyšší než 500, rychlost se zvýší o jednu jednotku. Na další úroveň se můžete dostat při 8 nebo 16 rychlostech. \n(3)5/OK - Pozastavit/Pokračovat; nahoru - otočit blok; vlevo/vpravo - přesunutí bloku doleva/doprava; dolů - přesunutí bloku dolů. \n(4)Zvuk lze zapnout/vypnout. \n(5)Mřížka na usnadňuje hraní.	(1)Istnieje siedem bloków, które są wyświetlane w różnych kolorach. \n(2)Prędkość początkowa w trybie łatwym wynosi 0. Gdy wynik przekroczy 500, prędkość wzrasta o jedną jednostkę. Możesz osiągnąć następny poziom przy 8 lub 16 prędkościach. \n(3)5/OK - Pauza/Kontynuacja; w górę - obróć blok; w lewo/prawo - przesuń blok w lewo/prawo; w dół - przesuń blok w dół. \n(4)Dźwięk można włączyć/wyłączyć. \n(5)Włączona siatka ułatwia grę.	(1) Hét blokk van, amelyek különböző színekkel jelennek meg. \n(2) A kezdősebesség egyszerű módban 0. Ha a pontszám meghaladja az 500-at, a sebesség egy egységgel nő. 8 vagy 16 sebességgel érheti el a következő szintet. \n(3)5/OK - Szünet/Folytatás; fel - forgatás blokk; bal/jobb - blokk mozgatása balra/jobbra; le - blokk mozgatása lefelé. \n(4)A hang be- és kikapcsolható. \n(5)A bekapcsolt rács megkönnyíti a játékot.	(1) On seitsemän lohkoa, jotka näytetään eri väreillä. \n(2) Aloitusnopeus helpossa tilassa on 0. Kun tulos on yli 500, nopeus kasvaa yhdellä yksiköllä. Voit päästä seuraavalle tasolle 8 tai 16 nopeudella. \n(3)5/OK - Tauko/Jatka; ylös - pyöritä lohkoa; vasen/oikea - siirrä lohkoa vasemmalle/oikealle; alas - siirrä lohko alas. \n(4)Ääni voidaan kytkeä päälle/pois. \n(5)Päällä oleva ruudukko helpottaa pelaamista.	(1) Det er syv blokker, som vises i forskjellige farger. \n(2)Starthastigheten i enkel modus er 0. Når poengsummen er over 500, øker hastigheten med én enhet. Du kan nå neste nivå med 8 eller 16 hastigheter. \n(3)5/OK - Pause/Fortsett; opp - roter blokken; venstre/høyre - flytt blokk til venstre/høyre; ned - flytt blokken ned. \n(4)Lyd kan slås på/av. \n(5)Rettet på gjør det enklere å spille.	(1) Existuje sedem blokov, ktoré sú zobrazené v rôznych farbách. \n(2)Počiatočná rýchlosť v jednoduchom režime je 0. Keď je skóre vyššie ako 500, rýchlosť sa zvýši o jednu jednotku. Ďalšiu úroveň môžete dosiahnuť pri 8 alebo 16 rýchlostiach. \n(3)5/OK - Pozastaviť/Pokračovať; hore - otočte blok; vľavo/vpravo - pohyb bloku doľava/doprava; dole - posunúť blok nadol. \n(4)Zvuk je možné zapnúť/vypnúť. \n(5) Mriežka uľahčuje hru.	(1)Er zijn zeven blokken, die in verschillende kleuren worden weergegeven. \n(2)De startsnelheid in de gemakkelijke modus is 0. Wanneer de score boven de 500 is, neemt de snelheid met één eenheid toe. Je kunt het volgende niveau bereiken met 8 of 16 snelheden. \n(3)5/OK - Pauze/Doorgaan; omhoog - blok roteren; links/rechts - blok naar links/rechts verplaatsen; omlaag - blok naar beneden verplaatsen. \n(4)Geluid kan aan/uit worden gezet. \n(5)Het raster maakt het spelen gemakkelijker.	(1) Det finns sju block, som visas i olika färger. \n(2)Starthastigheten i enkelt läge är 0. När poängen är över 500 ökar hastigheten med en enhet. Du kan nå nästa nivå med 8 eller 16 hastigheter. \n(3)5/OK - Pausa/Fortsätt; upp - rotera blocket; vänster/höger - flytta blocket vänster/höger; ner - flytta blocket ner. \n(4)Ljud kan slås på/av. \n(5)Gridet på gör spelet lättare.	(1) Postoji sedam blokova koji su prikazani u različitim bojama. \n(2) Početna brzina u jednostavnom načinu je 0. Kada je rezultat veći od 500, brzina se povećava za jednu jedinicu. Sljedeću razinu možete dosegnuti s 8 ili 16 brzina. \n(3)5/OK - Pauziraj/nastavi; gore - rotirati blok; lijevo/desno - pomakni blok lijevo/desno; dolje - pomaknite blok dolje. \n(4) Zvuk se može uključiti/isključiti. \n(5)Uključena mreža olakšava igru.	(1) Există șapte blocuri, care sunt afișate în culori diferite. \n(2)Viteza de pornire în modul ușor este 0. Când scorul este peste 500, viteza crește cu o unitate. Puteți ajunge la următorul nivel cu 8 sau 16 viteze. \n(3)5/OK - Pauză/Continuare; sus - rotiți blocul; stânga/dreapta - muta blocul stânga/dreapta; jos - muta blocul în jos. \n(4)Sunetul poate fi activat/dezactivat. \n(5) Grila activată facilitează jocul.	(1) Obstaja sedem blokov, ki so prikazani v različnih barvah. \n(2)Začetna hitrost v preprostem načinu je 0. Ko je rezultat nad 500, se hitrost poveča za eno enoto. Naslednjo stopnjo lahko dosežete z 8 ali 16 hitrostmi. \n(3)5/V redu - Premor/Nadaljuj; navzgor - zavrtite blok; levo/desno - premikanje bloka levo/desno; navzdol - premaknite blok navzdol. \n(4) Zvok je mogoče vklopiti/izklopiti. \n(5) Vklopljena mreža olajša igranje.	(1) Υπάρχουν επτά μπλοκ, τα οποία εμφανίζονται σε διαφορετικά χρώματα. \n(2) Η ταχύτητα εκκίνησης στην εύκολη λειτουργία είναι 0. Όταν η βαθμολογία είναι πάνω από 500, η ​​ταχύτητα αυξάνεται κατά μία μονάδα. Μπορείτε να φτάσετε στο επόμενο επίπεδο με 8 ή 16 ταχύτητες. \n(3)5/OK - Παύση/Συνέχεια. επάνω - περιστροφή μπλοκ αριστερά/δεξιά - μετακινήστε το μπλοκ αριστερά/δεξιά. κάτω - μετακινήστε το μπλοκ προς τα κάτω. \n(4) Ο ήχος μπορεί να ενεργ/απενεργ.\n(5)Το πλέγμα ενεργ διευκολύ το παιχνίδι.	(1) ישנם שבעה בלוקים, המוצגים בצבעים שונים. \n(2) מהירות ההתחלה במצב קל היא 0. כאשר הציון הוא מעל 500, המהירות עולה ביחידה אחת. אתה יכול להגיע לרמה הבאה עם 8 או 16 מהירויות. \n(3)5/אישור - השהה/המשך. למעלה - סובב בלוק; שמאלה/ימינה - הזז את הבלוק שמאלה/ימינה. למטה - הזיזו את הבלוק למטה. \n(4) ניתן להפעיל/לכבות את הצליל. \n(5) הרשת המופעלת הופכת את המשחק לקל יותר.	(1) Има седем блока, които се показват в различни цветове. \n(2) Началната скорост в лесен режим е 0. Когато резултатът е над 500, скоростта се увеличава с една единица. Можете да достигнете следващото ниво с 8 или 16 скорости. \n(3)5/OK - Пауза/Продължаване. нагоре - завъртете блока; ляво/надясно - преместете блока наляво/надясно. надолу - преместете блока надолу. \n(4) Звукът може да се включва/изключва. \n(5)Включената решетка прави играта по-лесна.	(1) सात ब्लॉक्स आहेत, जे वेगवेगळ्या रंगात प्रदर्शित होतात. \n(२) सोप्या मोडमध्ये सुरुवातीचा वेग ० आहे. जेव्हा स्कोअर ५०० पेक्षा जास्त असतो, तेव्हा वेग एका युनिटने वाढतो. तुम्ही 8 किंवा 16 वेगाने पुढील स्तरावर पोहोचू शकता. \n(३)५/ओके - विराम द्या/सुरू ठेवा. वर - ब्लॉक फिरवा; डावीकडे/उजवीकडे - ब्लॉक डावीकडे/उजवीकडे हलवा. खाली - ब्लॉक खाली हलवा. \n(४) आवाज चालू/बंद केला जाऊ शकतो. \n(५) ग्रिड चालू केल्याने गेम अधिक सोपा होतो.	(1) هفت بلوک وجود دارد که در رنگ های مختلف نمایش داده می شوند. \n(2) سرعت شروع در حالت آسان 0 است. وقتی امتیاز بیش از 500 باشد، سرعت یک واحد افزایش می یابد. شما می توانید با 8 یا 16 سرعت به سطح بعدی برسید. \n(3)5/OK - مکث/ادامه. بالا - چرخش بلوک؛ چپ/راست - بلوک را به چپ/راست حرکت دهید. پایین - بلوک را به پایین حرکت دهید. \n(4) صدا را می توان روشن/خاموش کرد. \n(5) روشن بودن شبکه بازی را آسان‌تر می‌کند.	(1) سات بلاکس ہیں، جو مختلف رنگوں میں دکھائے گئے ہیں۔ \n(2) آسان موڈ میں آغاز کی رفتار 0 ہے۔ جب سکور 500 سے زیادہ ہو جائے تو رفتار ایک یونٹ سے بڑھ جاتی ہے۔ آپ 8 یا 16 رفتار کے ساتھ اگلی سطح تک پہنچ سکتے ہیں۔ \n(3)5/ٹھیک ہے - روکیں/جاری رکھیں۔ اوپر - گھماؤ بلاک؛ بائیں/دائیں - بلاک کو بائیں/دائیں منتقل کریں۔ نیچے - بلاک کو نیچے منتقل کریں۔ \n(4) آواز کو آن/آف کیا جا سکتا ہے۔ \n(5)گرڈ کا آن ہونا گیم کو آسان بناتا ہے۔	(1) ஏழு தொகுதிகள் உள்ளன, அவை வெவ்வேறு வண்ணங்களில் காட்டப்படுகின்றன. \n(2) எளிதான பயன்முறையில் தொடக்க வேகம் 0. மதிப்பெண் 500க்கு மேல் இருக்கும்போது, ​​வேகம் ஒரு யூனிட் அதிகரிக்கிறது. 8 அல்லது 16 வேகத்தில் அடுத்த கட்டத்தை அடையலாம். \n(3)5/சரி - இடைநிறுத்தம்/தொடரவும். வரை - சுழற்று தொகுதி; இடது/வலது - தொகுதியை இடது/வலதுமாக நகர்த்தவும். கீழே - தொகுதியை கீழே நகர்த்தவும். \n(4) ஒலியை ஆன்/ஆஃப் செய்யலாம். \n(5) கட்டம் இயக்கப்பட்டிருப்பது விளையாட்டை எளிதாக்குகிறது.	(1) সাতটি ব্লক রয়েছে, যা বিভিন্ন রঙে প্রদর্শিত হয়। \n(2) সহজ মোডে শুরুর গতি 0। যখন স্কোর 500-এর বেশি হয়, তখন গতি এক একক বৃদ্ধি পায়। আপনি 8 বা 16 গতির সাথে পরবর্তী স্তরে পৌঁছাতে পারেন। \n(3)5/ঠিক আছে - বিরতি/চালিয়ে যান। আপ - ঘোরানো ব্লক; বাম/ডান - ব্লকটি বাম/ডানে সরান। নিচে - ব্লকটি নিচে সরান। \n(4) শব্দটি চালু/বন্ধ করা যেতে পারে। \n(5)গ্রিড চালু করা খেলাটিকে সহজ করে তোলে।	(1) ਇੱਥੇ ਸੱਤ ਬਲਾਕ ਹਨ, ਜੋ ਵੱਖ-ਵੱਖ ਰੰਗਾਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਪ੍ਰਦਰਸ਼ਿਤ ਹੁੰਦੇ ਹਨ। \n(2) ਆਸਾਨ ਮੋਡ ਵਿੱਚ ਸ਼ੁਰੂਆਤੀ ਗਤੀ 0 ਹੈ। ਜਦੋਂ ਸਕੋਰ 500 ਤੋਂ ਵੱਧ ਹੁੰਦਾ ਹੈ, ਤਾਂ ਗਤੀ ਇੱਕ ਯੂਨਿਟ ਦੁਆਰਾ ਵਧ ਜਾਂਦੀ ਹੈ। ਤੁਸੀਂ 8 ਜਾਂ 16 ਸਪੀਡ ਨਾਲ ਅਗਲੇ ਪੱਧਰ ਤੱਕ ਪਹੁੰਚ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ। \n(3)5/ਠੀਕ - ਰੋਕੋ/ਜਾਰੀ ਰੱਖੋ। ਉੱਪਰ - ਰੋਟੇਟ ਬਲਾਕ; ਖੱਬੇ/ਸੱਜੇ - ਬਲਾਕ ਨੂੰ ਖੱਬੇ/ਸੱਜੇ ਹਿਲਾਓ। ਹੇਠਾਂ - ਬਲਾਕ ਨੂੰ ਹੇਠਾਂ ਲੈ ਜਾਓ। \n(4) ਆਵਾਜ਼ ਨੂੰ ਚਾਲੂ/ਬੰਦ ਕੀਤਾ ਜਾ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ। \n(5)ਗਰਿੱਡ ਨੂੰ ਚਾਲੂ ਕੀਤਾ ਜਾਣਾ ਗੇਮ ਨੂੰ ਆਸਾਨ ਬਣਾਉਂਦਾ ਹੈ।	(1) వివిధ రంగులలో ప్రదర్శించబడే ఏడు బ్లాక్‌లు ఉన్నాయి. \n(2) ఈజీ మోడ్‌లో ప్రారంభ వేగం 0. స్కోర్ 500 కంటే ఎక్కువగా ఉన్నప్పుడు, వేగం ఒక యూనిట్ పెరుగుతుంది. మీరు 8 లేదా 16 వేగంతో తదుపరి స్థాయికి చేరుకోవచ్చు. \n(3)5/సరే - పాజ్/కొనసాగించు. పైకి - రొటేట్ బ్లాక్; ఎడమ/కుడి - బ్లాక్‌ను ఎడమ/కుడివైపు తరలించండి. డౌన్ - బ్లాక్‌ను క్రిందికి తరలించండి. \n(4) ధ్వనిని ఆన్/ఆఫ్ చేయవచ్చు. \n(5)గ్రిడ్ ఆన్ చేయడం వలన గేమ్ సులభతరం అవుతుంది.	(1) Існує сім блоків, які відображаються різними кольорами. \n(2) Початкова швидкість у легкому режимі дорівнює 0. Коли рахунок перевищує 500, швидкість збільшується на одиницю. Ви можете досягти наступного рівня з 8 або 16 швидкостями. \n(3)5/OK - Призупинити/Продовжити. вгору - поворот блоку; вліво/вправо - переміщення блоку вліво/вправо. down - перемістити блок вниз. \n(4) Звук можна вмикати/вимикати. \n(5) Увімкнена сітка полегшує гру.	(1) સાત બ્લોક્સ છે, જે વિવિધ રંગોમાં પ્રદર્શિત થાય છે. \n(2) સરળ મોડમાં શરૂઆતની ઝડપ 0 છે. જ્યારે સ્કોર 500 થી વધુ હોય, ત્યારે ઝડપ એક એકમથી વધે છે. તમે 8 અથવા 16 સ્પીડ સાથે આગલા સ્તર સુધી પહોંચી શકો છો. \n(3)5/ઓકે - થોભો/ચાલુ રાખો. ઉપર - બ્લોક ફેરવો; ડાબે/જમણે - બ્લોકને ડાબે/જમણે ખસેડો. નીચે - બ્લોકને નીચે ખસેડો. \n(4) અવાજ ચાલુ/બંધ કરી શકાય છે. \n(5) ગ્રીડ ચાલુ થવાથી રમત સરળ બને છે.	(1) ವಿವಿಧ ಬಣ್ಣಗಳಲ್ಲಿ ಪ್ರದರ್ಶಿಸಲಾದ ಏಳು ಬ್ಲಾಕ್‌ಗಳಿವೆ. \n(2) ಸುಲಭ ಮೋಡ್‌ನಲ್ಲಿ ಆರಂಭಿಕ ವೇಗವು 0 ಆಗಿದೆ. ಸ್ಕೋರ್ 500 ಕ್ಕಿಂತ ಹೆಚ್ಚಾದಾಗ, ವೇಗವು ಒಂದು ಘಟಕದಿಂದ ಹೆಚ್ಚಾಗುತ್ತದೆ. ನೀವು 8 ಅಥವಾ 16 ವೇಗಗಳೊಂದಿಗೆ ಮುಂದಿನ ಹಂತವನ್ನು ತಲುಪಬಹುದು. \n(3)5/ಸರಿ - ವಿರಾಮ/ಮುಂದುವರಿಯಿರಿ. ಅಪ್ - ತಿರುಗಿಸಿ ಬ್ಲಾಕ್; ಎಡ/ಬಲ - ಬ್ಲಾಕ್ ಅನ್ನು ಎಡ/ಬಲಕ್ಕೆ ಸರಿಸಿ. ಕೆಳಗೆ - ಬ್ಲಾಕ್ ಅನ್ನು ಕೆಳಕ್ಕೆ ಸರಿಸಿ. \n(4) ಧ್ವನಿಯನ್ನು ಆನ್/ಆಫ್ ಮಾಡಬಹುದು. \n(5)ಗ್ರಿಡ್ ಆನ್ ಆಗಿರುವುದು ಆಟವನ್ನು ಸುಲಭಗೊಳಿಸುತ್ತದೆ.	(1) Kunamabhulokhi ayisikhombisa, aboniswa ngemibala ehlukene. \n(2) Isivinini sokuqala kumodi elula ngu-0. Uma isikolo singaphezu kuka-500, isivinini sikhuphuka ngeyunithi eyodwa. Ungakwazi ukufinyelela ezingeni elilandelayo ngesivinini 8 noma 16. \n(3)5/KULUNGILE - Misa isikhashana/Qhubeka. up - zungeza block; kwesokunxele/kwesokudla - hambisa ibhlogo kwesokunxele/kwesokudla. phansi - hambisa ibhulokhi phansi. \n(4) Umsindo ungavulwa/ucishwe. \n(5)Ukuvulwa kwegridi kwenza igeyimu ibe lula.	(1) Kukho iibhloko ezisixhenxe, eziboniswe ngemibala eyahlukeneyo. \n(2) Isantya sokuqala kwimowudi elula ngu-0. Xa amanqaku angaphezulu kwama-500, isantya sonyuka ngeyunithi enye. Ungafikelela kwinqanaba elilandelayo kunye 8 okanye 16 izantya. \n(3)5/Kulungile - Misa/Qhubeka. phezulu - ibhloko yokujikeleza; ekhohlo/ekunene - hambisa ibhloko ekhohlo/ekunene. phantsi - hambisa ibhloko ezantsi. \n(4) Isandi sinokuvulwa/sicinywe. \n(5)Ukuvulwa kwegridi kwenza umdlalo ube lula.	(1) Kuna vitalu saba, ambavyo vinaonyeshwa kwa rangi tofauti. \n(2) Kasi ya kuanzia katika hali rahisi ni 0. Alama ikiwa zaidi ya 500, kasi huongezeka kwa uniti moja. Unaweza kufikia kiwango kinachofuata kwa kasi 8 au 16. \n(3)5/Sawa - Sitisha/Endelea. juu - kuzuia mzunguko; kushoto / kulia - songa kizuizi kushoto / kulia. chini - songa kizuizi chini. \n(4) Sauti inaweza kuwashwa/kuzimwa. \n(5) Gridi kuwashwa hurahisisha mchezo.	(1) Daar is sewe blokke wat in verskillende kleure vertoon word. \n(2) Die beginspoed in maklike modus is 0. Wanneer die telling meer as 500 is, verhoog die spoed met een eenheid. Jy kan die volgende vlak bereik met 8 of 16 snelhede. \n(3)5/OK - Onderbreek/Gaan voort. op - draai blok; links/regs - beweeg die blok links/regs. af - skuif die blok af. \n(4) Die klank kan aan/af geskakel word. \n(5)Die rooster wat aangeskakel word, maak die speletjie makliker.	(1) Yra septyni blokai, kurie rodomi skirtingomis spalvomis. \n(2) Pradinis greitis lengvuoju režimu yra 0. Kai rezultatas viršija 500, greitis padidėja vienu vienetu. Galite pasiekti kitą lygį naudodami 8 arba 16 greičių. \n(3)5/Gerai – pristabdyti/tęsti. aukštyn - pasukti bloką; kairėn/dešinėn – perkelkite bloką į kairę/dešinę. žemyn - perkelkite bloką žemyn. \n(4) Garsą galima įjungti/išjungti. \n(5)Įjungtas tinklelis palengvina žaidimą.	(1) Ir septiņi bloki, kas tiek parādīti dažādās krāsās. \n(2) Sākuma ātrums vienkāršajā režīmā ir 0. Ja rezultāts pārsniedz 500, ātrums palielinās par vienu vienību. Jūs varat sasniegt nākamo līmeni ar 8 vai 16 ātrumiem. \n(3)5/OK — Pauze/Turpināt. uz augšu - pagriezt bloku; pa kreisi/pa labi - pārvietojiet bloku pa kreisi/pa labi. uz leju - pārvietojiet bloku uz leju. \n(4) Skaņu var ieslēgt/izslēgt. \n(5)Ieslēgtais režģis atvieglo spēli.	(1) Seal on seitse plokki, mis kuvatakse erinevates värvides. \n(2) Lihtrežiimis on stardikiirus 0. Kui tulemus on üle 500, suureneb kiirus ühe ühiku võrra. Järgmisele tasemele saate jõuda 8 või 16 kiirusega. \n(3)5/OK – peata/jätka. üles - pööra plokki; vasakule/paremale – liigutage plokki vasakule/paremale. alla - liigutage plokk alla. \n(4) Heli saab sisse/välja lülitada. \n(5)Sisse lülitatud ruudustik muudab mängu lihtsamaks.	(1) Կան յոթ բլոկներ, որոնք ցուցադրվում են տարբեր գույներով: \n(2) Հեշտ ռեժիմում մեկնարկային արագությունը 0 է: Երբ միավորը գերազանցում է 500-ը, արագությունը մեծանում է մեկ միավորով: Դուք կարող եք հասնել հաջորդ մակարդակին 8 կամ 16 արագությամբ: \n(3)5/OK - Դադար/շարունակել: վերև - պտտել բլոկը; ձախ/աջ - տեղափոխեք բլոկը ձախ/աջ: ներքև - բլոկը տեղափոխել ներքև: \n(4) Ձայնը կարելի է միացնել/անջատել։ \n(5) Ցանցի միացումը հեշտացնում է խաղը:	(1) არის შვიდი ბლოკი, რომლებიც გამოსახულია სხვადასხვა ფერებში. \n(2) მარტივი რეჟიმში საწყისი სიჩქარე არის 0. როდესაც ქულა 500-ზე მეტია, სიჩქარე იზრდება ერთი ერთეულით. თქვენ შეგიძლიათ მიაღწიოთ შემდეგ დონეს 8 ან 16 სიჩქარით. \n(3)5/OK - პაუზა/გაგრძელება. up - როტაცია ბლოკი; მარცხნივ/მარჯვნივ - გადაიტანეთ ბლოკი მარცხნივ/მარჯვნივ. ქვემოთ - გადაიტანეთ ბლოკი ქვემოთ. \n(4) ხმის ჩართვა/გამორთვა შესაძლებელია. \n(5) ბადის ჩართვა თამაშს ამარტივებს.	(1) Există șapte blocuri, care sunt afișate în culori diferite. \n(2) Viteza de pornire în modul ușor este 0. Când scorul este peste 500, viteza crește cu o unitate. Puteți ajunge la următorul nivel cu 8 sau 16 viteze. \n(3)5/OK - Pauză/Continuare. sus - rotiți blocul; stânga/dreapta - mutați blocul la stânga/dreapta. jos - mutați blocul în jos. \n(4) Sunetul poate fi activat/dezactivat. \n(5) Grila activată face jocul mai ușor.	(1) ഏഴ് ബ്ലോക്കുകൾ ഉണ്ട്, അവ വ്യത്യസ്ത നിറങ്ങളിൽ പ്രദർശിപ്പിച്ചിരിക്കുന്നു. \n(2) ഈസി മോഡിൽ ആരംഭ വേഗത 0 ആണ്. സ്കോർ 500-ൽ കൂടുതലാകുമ്പോൾ, വേഗത ഒരു യൂണിറ്റ് വർദ്ധിക്കും. 8 അല്ലെങ്കിൽ 16 വേഗതയിൽ നിങ്ങൾക്ക് അടുത്ത ലെവലിൽ എത്താം. \n(3)5/ശരി - താൽക്കാലികമായി നിർത്തുക/തുടരുക. മുകളിലേക്ക് - തിരിക്കുക ബ്ലോക്ക്; ഇടത്/വലത് - ബ്ലോക്ക് ഇടത്തേക്ക്/വലത്തേക്ക് നീക്കുക. താഴേക്ക് - ബ്ലോക്ക് താഴേക്ക് നീക്കുക. \n(4) ശബ്ദം ഓൺ/ഓഫ് ചെയ്യാം. \n(5)ഗ്രിഡ് ഓണാക്കിയത് ഗെയിം എളുപ്പമാക്കുന്നു.	(1) ସାତଟି ବ୍ଲକ୍ ଅଛି, ଯାହା ବିଭିନ୍ନ ରଙ୍ଗରେ ପ୍ରଦର୍ଶିତ ହୁଏ | \n (2) ସହଜ ମୋଡ୍ ରେ ପ୍ରାରମ୍ଭିକ ଗତି 0 ଅଟେ | ଯେତେବେଳେ ସ୍କୋର 500 ରୁ ଅଧିକ ହୁଏ, ଗତି ଗୋଟିଏ ୟୁନିଟ୍ ଦ୍ୱାରା ଯୋଗ କରିଥାଏ | ଆପଣ 8 କିମ୍ବା 16 ଗତି ସହିତ ପରବର୍ତ୍ତୀ ସ୍ତରକୁ ଯାଇପାରିବେ | \n (3) 5 / ଠିକ ଅଛି - ବିରତି / ଜାରି ରଖନ୍ତୁ | ଅପ୍ - ଘୂର୍ଣ୍ଣନ ବ୍ଲକ; ବାମ / ଡାହାଣ - ବ୍ଲକକୁ ବାମ / ଡାହାଣକୁ ଘୁଞ୍ଚାନ୍ତୁ | ତଳକୁ - ବ୍ଲକକୁ ତଳକୁ ଘୁଞ୍ଚାନ୍ତୁ | \n (4) ଧ୍ୱନି ଅନ୍ / ଅଫ୍ ହୋଇପାରେ | \n (5) ଗ୍ରୀଡ୍ ଅନ୍ ହେବା ଖେଳକୁ ସହଜ କରିଥାଏ |	(1) Janë shtatë blloqe, të cilat shfaqen me ngjyra të ndryshme. \n(2) Shpejtësia e fillimit në modalitetin e lehtë është 0. Kur rezultati është mbi 500, shpejtësia rritet me një njësi. Ju mund të arrini nivelin tjetër me 8 ose 16 shpejtësi. \n(3)5/OK - Ndalo/Vazhdo. lart - blloku i rrotullimit; majtas/djathtas - lëvizni bllokun majtas/djathtas. poshtë - zhvendosni bllokun poshtë. \n(4) Tingulli mund të ndizet/fiket. \n(5) Aktivizimi i rrjetit e bën lojën më të lehtë.	(১) সাতটা ব্লক আছে, যিবোৰ বিভিন্ন ৰঙত প্ৰদৰ্শিত হয়। \n(2) সহজ অৱস্থাত আৰম্ভণিৰ গতি 0. যেতিয়া স্ক'ৰ 500 ৰ ওপৰত হয়, গতি এটা একক বৃদ্ধি পায়। ৮ বা ১৬ গতিৰে পৰৱৰ্তী স্তৰত উপনীত হ’ব পাৰে। \n(3)5/ঠিক আছে - বিৰতি/অব্যাহত ৰাখক। আপ - ঘূৰোৱা ব্লক; বাওঁ/সোঁফালে - ব্লকটো বাওঁ/সোঁফালে লৈ যাওক। down - ব্লক তললৈ লৈ যাওক। \n(৪) শব্দটো অন/অফ কৰিব পাৰি। \n(5)গ্ৰিড অন কৰাটোৱে খেলখন সহজ কৰি তোলে।	(1) Müxtəlif rənglərdə nümayiş etdirilən yeddi blok var. \n(2) Asan rejimdə başlanğıc sürəti 0-dır. Hesab 500-dən çox olduqda sürət bir vahid artır. 8 və ya 16 sürətlə növbəti səviyyəyə çata bilərsiniz. \n(3)5/OK - Pauza/Davam et. yuxarı - bloku döndərin; sol/sağ - bloku sola/sağa köçürün. aşağı - bloku aşağı hərəkət etdirin. \n(4) Səs yandırıla/söndürilə bilər. \n(5)Aktiv olan şəbəkə oyunu asanlaşdırır.	（1）有七個積木，佢哋用唔同嘅顏色顯示\n（2）簡單模式嘅起始速度係0。當分數超過500嗰陣，速度會增加一個單位。你可以用8或者16個速度去到下一個級別。\n（3）5/確定 - 暫停/繼續。向上 - 旋轉塊；左/右 - 將個塊向左/向右移動。向下 - 將個塊向下移動。 \n(4) 聲音可以開/關。 \n （5）開緊嘅格令到遊戲更加容易。	(1) Hi ha set formes de bloc, que es mostren en diferents colors. \n(2)La velocitat inicial en fàcil és 0. Quan la puntuació supera els 500, la velocitat augmentarà una unitat. Podeu entrar al següent nivell amb 8 o 16 velocitats. \n(3)5/D'acord - pausa/continua; amunt - girar el bloc; esquerra/dreta - mou el bloc esquerra/dreta; avall - mou el bloc cap a la part inferior. \n(4)El so pot estar activat/desactivat. \n(5)La graella activada us facilitarà.	(1) Il y a sept formes de blocs, affichées dans différentes couleurs. \n(2)La vitesse initiale en mode facile est de 0. Lorsque le score dépasse 500, la vitesse augmente d'une unité. Vous pouvez accéder au prochain niveau à 8 ou 16 vitesses. \n(3)5/OK - pause/continuer ; vers le haut - faire pivoter le bloc ; gauche/droite - déplace le bloc vers la gauche/droite; bas - déplace le bloc vers le bas. \n(4)Le son peut être activé/désactivé. \n(5)La grille activée vous facilitera la tâche.	(1) Það eru sjö form af blokk, sýnd í mismunandi litum. \n(2)Upphafshraðinn í easy er 0. Þegar einkunn er komin yfir 500 mun hraðinn auka einingu. Þú getur farið inn á næsta stig á 8 eða 16 hraða. \n(3)5/Í lagi - hlé/halda áfram; upp - snúa blokk; vinstri/hægri - færðu blokk til vinstri/hægri;niður - færðu blokk til botns. \n(4) Hægt er að kveikja/slökkva á hljóði. \n(5)Rit á mun auðvelda þér.	(1) Hay siete formas de bloques, que se muestran en diferentes colores. \n(2) La velocidad inicial en el nivel fácil es 0. Cuando la puntuación supere los 500, la velocidad aumentará una unidad. Puede ingresar al siguiente nivel con una velocidad de 8 o 16. \n(3) 5/OK: pausa/continuar; arriba: rotar el bloque; izquierda/derecha: mover el bloque a la izquierda/derecha; abajo: mover el bloque al fondo. \n(4) El sonido puede activarse o desactivarse. \n(5) La cuadrícula activada lo facilitará.	(1) Постојат седум форми на блок, прикажани во различни бои. \n(2)Почетната брзина во easy е 0. Кога резултатот е над 500, брзината ќе се зголеми за единица. Можете да влезете во следното ниво со 8 или 16 брзини. \n(3)5/OK - пауза/продолжи; нагоре - ротирачки блок; лево/десно - поместете го блокот лево/десно; надолу - поместете го блокот до дното. \n(4)Звукот може да се вклучува/исклучува. \n(5)Вклучената мрежа ќе ви олесни.	(1) Existem sete formas de bloco, exibidas em cores diferentes. \n(2) A velocidade inicial no fácil é 0. Quando a pontuação passa de 500, a velocidade aumentará uma unidade. Você pode entrar no próximo nível na velocidade 8 ou 16. \n(3) 5/OK - pausar/continuar; cima - girar bloco; esquerda/direita - mover bloco para a esquerda/direita; baixo - mover bloco para o fundo. \n(4) O som pode ser ligado/desligado. \n(5) A grade ligada facilitará você.	(1) Постоји седам облика блока, приказаних у различитим бојама. \н(2)Иницијална брзина у лаком је 0. Када резултат пређе 500, брзина ће се повећати за јединицу. Можете ући у следећи ниво на 8 или 16 брзина. \н(3)5/ОК - пауза/настави; горе - ротирати блок; лево/десно - помери блок лево/десно; доле - помери блок на дно. \н(4)Звук може бити укључен/искључен. \н(5) Мрежа ће вам олакшати.	(1) Ho na le libopeho tse supileng tsa boloko, tse bonts'itsoeng ka mebala e fapaneng. \n(2)Lebelo la ho qala ka bonolo ke 0. Ha lintlha li fetile 500, lebelo le tla eketsa yuniti. O ka kenya boemo bo latelang ka lebelo la 8 kapa 16. \n(3)5/OK - emisa/tswella; holimo - potoloha block; ka ho le letšehali/ ho le letona - suthisa boloko ka ho le letšehali/ ka ho le letona; tlaase - tsamaisa boloko ho ea tlaase. \n(4)Modumo o ka bulwa/wa tima. \n(5) Grid on e tla u thusa.	(1)May pitong hugis ng bloke, na ipinapakita sa iba't ibang kulay. \n(2)Ang paunang bilis sa madaling ay 0. Kapag ang marka ay lumampas sa 500, ang bilis ay tataas ang isang yunit. Maaari kang pumasok sa susunod na antas sa 8 o 16 na bilis. \n(3)5/OK - pause/continue;up - rotate block;left/right - move block left/right;down ​​- move block to the bottom.\n(4)Maaaring on/off ang tunog. \n(5)Mapapadali ka ng grid on.	(1)There are seven shapes of block, displayed in different colors. \n(2)Initial speed in easy is 0. When score is past 500, the speed will increase a unit. You can enter the next level on 8 or 16 speed. \n(3)5/OK - pause/continue; up - rotate block; left/right - move block left/right;down - move block to the bottom. \n(4)Sound can be on/off. \n(5)Grid on will facilitate you.	(1) Akwai nau'i bakwai na toshe, wanda aka nuna a cikin launi daban-daban. \n(2)Tsarin farko a cikin sauƙi shine 0. Idan maki ya wuce 500, gudun zai ƙara raka'a. Kuna iya shigar da mataki na gaba akan saurin 8 ko 16. \n (3)5/Ok - dakata/ci gaba; sama - jujjuya toshe; hagu/dama - matsar da toshe hagu/dama; ƙasa - matsar da toshe zuwa ƙasa. \n (4) Ana iya kunna/kashe sauti. \n(5)Grid on zai sauƙaƙa muku.	(1) Awọn apẹrẹ meje wa ti bulọọki, ti o han ni awọn awọ oriṣiriṣi. \n(2)Iyara akọkọ ni irọrun jẹ 0. Nigbati Dimegilio ba kọja 500, iyara yoo pọ si ẹyọ kan. O le tẹ ipele atẹle sii lori iyara 8 tabi 16. \n (3)5/DARA - da duro/tesiwaju; soke - yi Àkọsílẹ; osi/ọtun - gbe bulọọki si osi/ọtun; isalẹ - gbe Àkọsílẹ si isalẹ. \n(4)Ohùn le wa ni titan/pa. \n(5)Gídíò yíò rọrùn fún ọ.	(1) Әртүрлі түстерде көрсетілген жеті блок пішіні бар. \n(2)Оңайдағы бастапқы жылдамдық - 0. Ұпай 500-ден асқанда, жылдамдық бірлікті арттырады. Келесі деңгейге 8 немесе 16 жылдамдықпен кіруге болады. \n(3)5/OK - кідірту/жалғастыру; жоғары - айналдыру блогы; солға/оңға - блокты солға/оңға жылжыту; төмен - блокты төменге жылжыту. \n(4)Дыбыс қосулы/өшірулі болуы мүмкін. \n(5) Тор қосулы болуы сізге көмектеседі.	(1)Zazpi bloke-forma daude, kolore ezberdinetan bistaratzen direnak. \n(2)Hasierako abiadura 0 da errazan. Puntuazioa 500etik gorakoa denean, abiadurak unitate bat handituko du. Hurrengo mailan sar zaitezke 8 edo 16 abiaduran. \n(3)5/Ados - pausatu/jarraitu; gora - biratu blokea; ezkerrera/eskuinera - mugitu blokea ezkerrera/eskuinera;behera - mugitu blokea behealdera. \n(4)Soinua piztu/desaktibatu daiteke. \n(5)Grid on erraztuko zaitu.	(1)May pitong hugis ng bloke, na ipinapakita sa iba't ibang kulay. \n(2)Ang paunang bilis sa madaling ay 0. Kapag ang marka ay lumampas sa 500, ang bilis ay tataas ang isang yunit. Maaari kang pumasok sa susunod na antas sa 8 o 16 na bilis. \n(3)5/OK - i-pause/ituloy; pataas - paikutin ang bloke; kaliwa/kanan - ilipat ang bloke pakaliwa/kanan; pababa - ilipat ang bloke sa ibaba. \n(4)Maaaring i-on/i-off ang tunog. \n(5)Mapapadali ka ng grid on.	(1) Hai sete formas de bloque, mostradas en diferentes cores. \n(2)A velocidade inicial en fácil é 0. Cando a puntuación supera os 500, a velocidade aumentará unha unidade. Podes entrar no seguinte nivel en 8 ou 16 velocidades. \n(3)5/OK - pausar/continuar; arriba - xirar o bloque; esquerda/dereita - mover o bloque á esquerda/dereita; abaixo - mover o bloque cara abaixo. \n(4)O son pode estar activado/desactivado. \n(5)Grid on facilitarache.	(1) E nwere ụdị asaa nke ngọngọ, gosipụtara na agba dị iche iche. \n(2)Ọsọ mbụ dị mfe bụ 0. Mgbe akara gafere 500, ọsọ ga-abawanye otu nkeji. Ị nwere ike ịbanye ọkwa na-esote na ọsọ 8 ma ọ bụ 16. \n(3)5/OK - kwụsịtụ/ gaba n'ihu; elu - bugharia ngọngọ; aka ekpe/n'aka nri - bugharịa ngọngọ aka ekpe/aka nri; ala - bugharịa ngọngọ gaa na ala. \n(4)ụda nwere ike ịgbanwu/ gbanyụọ. \n(5)Grid on ga-enyere gị aka.	(1) Tá seacht gcruth bloc, ar taispeáint i dathanna éagsúla. \n(2)Is é 0 an luas tosaigh i éasca. Nuair a bhíonn an scór thart ar 500, méadóidh an luas aonad. Is féidir leat dul isteach ar an chéad leibhéal eile ar 8 nó 16 luas. \n(3)5/OK - sos/lean ar aghaidh; suas - rothlú bloc; clé/deas - bog an bloc ar chlé/ar dheis; síos - bog an bloc go dtí an bun. \n(4)Is féidir le fuaim a bheith curtha ar siúl/ as. \n(5)Éascóidh an eangach tú.	(၁) အရောင်မျိုးစုံဖြင့် ပြသထားသော ဘလောက်ပုံစံ ခုနစ်မျိုးရှိသည်။ \n(2)လွယ်ကူသော ကနဦးအမြန်နှုန်းမှာ 0 ဖြစ်သည်။ ရမှတ် 500 ကျော်သွားသောအခါ၊ အမြန်နှုန်းသည် ယူနစ်တစ်ခုတိုးလာမည်ဖြစ်သည်။ 8 သို့မဟုတ် 16 အမြန်နှုန်းဖြင့်နောက်ထပ်အဆင့်ကိုသင်ဝင်ရောက်နိုင်သည်။ \n(3)5/OK - ခေတ္တရပ်ရန်/ဆက်လုပ်ရန်။ up - rotate block; ဘယ်/ညာ - ဘလောက်ကို ဘယ်/ညာ ရွှေ့ပါ၊ အောက်မှ အောက်ခြေသို့ ပိတ်ဆို့ပါ။ \n(4) အသံဖွင့်/ပိတ်နိုင်သည်။ \n(5) Grid on က သင့်ကို အဆင်ပြေချောမွေ့စေမှာပါ။	(1​) ມີ​ເຈັດ​ຮູບ​ຮ່າງ​ຂອງ​ຕັນ​, ສະ​ແດງ​ໃນ​ສີ​ທີ່​ແຕກ​ຕ່າງ​ກັນ​. \n(2)ຄວາມໄວເບື້ອງຕົ້ນໃນງ່າຍແມ່ນ 0. ເມື່ອຄະແນນເກີນ 500, ຄວາມໄວຈະເພີ່ມຂຶ້ນໜຶ່ງໜ່ວຍ. ທ່ານສາມາດເຂົ້າໄປໃນລະດັບຕໍ່ໄປໃນ 8 ຫຼື 16 ຄວາມໄວ. \n(3)5/OK - ຢຸດຊົ່ວຄາວ/ສືບຕໍ່; up - rotate block; ຊ້າຍ / ຂວາ - ຍ້າຍບລັອກຊ້າຍ / ຂວາ; ລົງ - ຍ້າຍບລັອກໄປທາງລຸ່ມ. \n(4) ສາມາດເປີດ/ປິດສຽງໄດ້. \n(5)ການເປີດ Grid ຈະອຳນວຍຄວາມສະດວກແກ່ເຈົ້າ.	(1​) មាន​រាង​ប្រាំពីរ​នៃ​ប្លុក​ដែល​បង្ហាញ​ជា​ពណ៌​ផ្សេង​គ្នា​។ \n(2)ល្បឿនដំបូងក្នុងភាពងាយស្រួលគឺ 0។ នៅពេលពិន្ទុលើសពី 500 ល្បឿននឹងកើនឡើងមួយឯកតា។ អ្នកអាចចូលទៅក្នុងកម្រិតបន្ទាប់នៅលើល្បឿន 8 ឬ 16 ។ \n(3)5/យល់ព្រម - ផ្អាក/បន្ត; ឡើងលើ - បង្វិលប្លុក; ឆ្វេង / ស្តាំ - ផ្លាស់ទីប្លុកទៅឆ្វេង / ស្តាំ; ចុះក្រោម - ផ្លាស់ទីប្លុកទៅបាត។ \n(4) សំឡេងអាចបើក/បិទបាន។ \n(5) Grid on នឹងជួយសម្រួលដល់អ្នក។	(1) 블록 모양은 7가지이며, 다른 색상으로 표시됩니다. \n(2) 쉬운 단계의 초기 속도는 0입니다. 점수가 500을 넘으면 속도가 한 단위 증가합니다. 8 또는 16 속도로 다음 레벨에 진입할 수 있습니다. \n(3) 5/확인 - 일시 중지/계속; 위로 - 블록 회전; 왼쪽/오른쪽 - 블록을 왼쪽/오른쪽으로 이동; 아래로 - 블록을 맨 아래로 이동. \n(4) 소리를 켜거나 끌 수 있습니다. \n(5) 그리드를 켜면 더 편리합니다.	(၁) အရောင်မျိုးစုံဖြင့် ပြသထားသော ဘလောက်ပုံစံ ခုနစ်မျိုးရှိသည်။ \n(2)လွယ်ကူသော ကနဦးအမြန်နှုန်းမှာ 0 ဖြစ်သည်။ ရမှတ် 500 ကျော်သွားသောအခါ၊ အမြန်နှုန်းသည် ယူနစ်တစ်ခုတိုးလာမည်ဖြစ်သည်။ 8 သို့မဟုတ် 16 အမြန်နှုန်းဖြင့်နောက်ထပ်အဆင့်ကိုသင်ဝင်ရောက်နိုင်သည်။ \n(3)5/OK - ခေတ္တရပ်ရန်/ဆက်လုပ်ရန်။ up - rotate block; ဘယ်/ညာ - ဘလောက်ကို ဘယ်/ညာ ရွှေ့ပါ၊ အောက်မှ အောက်ခြေသို့ ပိတ်ဆို့ပါ။ \n(4) အသံဖွင့်/ပိတ်နိုင်သည်။ \n(5) Grid on က သင့်ကို အဆင်ပြေချောမွေ့စေမှာပါ။	
STR_GX_TETRIS_REPORT_SCORE	GAME	UNLIM	tetris	Your score is %d, the highest score in this level is %d. Try again!	您的分數是 %d，該級別的最高分數是 %d。再試一次！	您的得分为 %d，本关最高得分为 %d。再试一次！	คะแนนของคุณคือ %d คะแนนสูงสุดในด่านนี้คือ %d ลองอีกครั้ง!	Tu puntuación es %d, la puntuación más alta en este nivel es %d. ¡Inténtalo de nuevo!	Votre score est de %d, le score le plus élevé de ce niveau est de %d. Réessayez !	Ihre Punktzahl beträgt %d, die höchste Punktzahl in diesem Level beträgt %d. Versuchen Sie es erneut!	Ваш счет %d, наивысший счет на этом уровне %d. Попробуйте еще раз!	Il tuo punteggio è %d, il punteggio più alto in questo livello è %d. Riprova!	نتيجتك هي %d، وأعلى نتيجة في هذا المستوى هي %d. حاول مرة أخرى!	A sua pontuação é %d, a pontuação mais elevada neste nível é %d. Tente novamente!	Puanınız %d, bu seviyedeki en yüksek puan %d. Tekrar deneyin!	Điểm số của bạn là %d, điểm số cao nhất trong cấp độ này là %d. Hãy thử lại!	Skor Anda adalah %d, skor tertinggi di level ini adalah %d. Coba lagi!	Markah anda ialah %d, markah tertinggi dalam tahap ini ialah %d. Cuba lagi!	आपका स्कोर %d है, इस लेवल में सबसे ज़्यादा स्कोर %d है। फिर से कोशिश करें!	Din score er %d, den højeste score på dette niveau er %d. Prøv igen!	Vaše skóre je %d, nejvyšší skóre v této úrovni je %d. Zkuste to znovu!	Twój wynik to %d, najwyższy wynik na tym poziomie to %d. Spróbuj ponownie!	Az Ön pontszáma %d, a legmagasabb pontszám ezen a szinten: %d. Próbáld újra!	Pistemääräsi on %d, tämän tason korkein pistemäärä on %d. Yritä uudelleen!	Poengsummen din er %d, den høyeste poengsummen på dette nivået er %d. Prøv igjen!	Vaše skóre je %d, najvyššie skóre na tejto úrovni je %d. Skúste to znova!	Je score is %d, de hoogste score in dit level is %d. Probeer het opnieuw!	Din poäng är %d, den högsta poängen på denna nivå är %d. Försök igen!	Vaš rezultat je %d, najveći rezultat na ovoj razini je %d. Pokušajte ponovno!	Scorul tău este %d, cel mai mare scor la acest nivel este %d. Încearcă din nou!	Vaš rezultat je %d, najvišji rezultat na tej ravni je %d. Poskusite znova!	Η βαθμολογία σας είναι %d, η υψηλότερη βαθμολογία σε αυτό το επίπεδο είναι %d. Δοκιμάστε ξανά!	הציון שלך הוא %d, הציון הגבוה ביותר ברמה זו הוא %d. נסה שוב!	Вашият резултат е %d, най-високият резултат на това ниво е %d. Опитайте отново!	तुमचा स्कोअर %d आहे, या स्तरातील सर्वोच्च स्कोअर %d आहे. पुन्हा प्रयत्न करा!	امتیاز شما %d است، بالاترین امتیاز در این سطح %d است. دوباره امتحان کنید!	آپ کا سکور %d ہے، اس لیول میں سب سے زیادہ سکور %d ہے۔ دوبارہ کوشش کریں!	உங்கள் மதிப்பெண் %d, இந்த நிலையில் அதிகபட்ச மதிப்பெண் %d ஆகும். மீண்டும் முயற்சிக்கவும்!	আপনার স্কোর হল %d, এই স্তরের সর্বোচ্চ স্কোর হল %d। আবার চেষ্টা করুন!	ਤੁਹਾਡਾ ਸਕੋਰ %d ਹੈ, ਇਸ ਪੱਧਰ ਵਿੱਚ ਸਭ ਤੋਂ ਵੱਧ ਸਕੋਰ %d ਹੈ। ਫਿਰ ਕੋਸ਼ਿਸ਼ ਕਰੋ!	మీ స్కోర్ %d, ఈ స్థాయిలో అత్యధిక స్కోర్ %d. మళ్లీ ప్రయత్నించండి!	Ваш бал %d, найвищий бал на цьому рівні %d. Спробуйте знову!	તમારો સ્કોર %d છે, આ સ્તરનો સૌથી વધુ સ્કોર %d છે. ફરી પ્રયાસ કરો!	ನಿಮ್ಮ ಸ್ಕೋರ್ %d ಆಗಿದೆ, ಈ ಹಂತದಲ್ಲಿ ಅತ್ಯಧಿಕ ಸ್ಕೋರ್ %d ಆಗಿದೆ. ಮತ್ತೆ ಪ್ರಯತ್ನಿಸಿ!	Isikolo sakho ngu-%d, amaphuzu aphezulu kuleli zinga ngu-%d. Zama futhi!	Amanqaku akho yi-%d, awona manqaku aphezulu kulo mgangatho yi-%d. Zama kwakhona!	Alama yako ni %d, alama ya juu zaidi katika kiwango hiki ni %d. Jaribu tena!	Jou telling is %d, die hoogste telling in hierdie vlak is %d. Probeer weer!	Jūsų balas yra %d, aukščiausias balas šiame lygyje yra %d. Bandyk dar kartą!	Jūsu rezultāts ir %d, augstākais rezultāts šajā līmenī ir %d. Mēģiniet vēlreiz!	Teie skoor on %d, kõrgeim tulemus sellel tasemel on %d. Proovi uuesti!	Ձեր միավորը %d է, այս մակարդակի ամենաբարձր միավորը %d է: Կրկին փորձեք:	თქვენი ქულაა %d, უმაღლესი ქულა ამ დონეზე არის %d. ისევ სცადე!	Scorul tău este %d, cel mai mare scor la acest nivel este %d. Încearcă din nou!	നിങ്ങളുടെ സ്കോർ %d ആണ്, ഈ ലെവലിലെ ഏറ്റവും ഉയർന്ന സ്കോർ %d ആണ്. വീണ്ടും ശ്രമിക്കുക!	ଆପଣଙ୍କର ସ୍କୋର ହେଉଛି% d, ଏହି ସ୍ତରରେ ସର୍ବାଧିକ ସ୍କୋର ହେଉଛି% d | ପୁନର୍ବାର ଚେଷ୍ଟା କରନ୍ତୁ!	Rezultati juaj është %d, rezultati më i lartë në këtë nivel është %d. Provo sërish!	আপোনাৰ নম্বৰ হৈছে %d, এই স্তৰৰ সৰ্বোচ্চ নম্বৰ হৈছে %d । আকৌ এবাৰ চেষ্টা কৰক!	Hesabınız %d, bu səviyyədə ən yüksək xal %d-dir. Yenidən cəhd edin!	你嘅分數係 % 啲，呢個級別嘅最高分數係 % 啲，再試一次！	La teva puntuació és %d, la puntuació més alta d'aquest nivell és %d. Torna-ho a provar!	Votre pointage est %d, le score le plus élevé à ce niveau est %d. Essayer encore une fois!	Einkunnin þín er %d, hæsta stigið á þessu stigi er %d. Reyndu aftur!	Tu puntuación es %d, la puntuación más alta en este nivel es %d. ¡Inténtalo de nuevo!	Вашиот резултат е %d, највисокиот резултат на ова ниво е %d. Обидете се повторно!	Sua pontuação é %d, a pontuação mais alta neste nível é %d. Tente novamente!	Ваш резултат је %д, највиши резултат на овом нивоу је %д. Покушајте поново!	Lintlha tsa hau ke %d, lintlha tse holimo boemong bona ke %d. Leka hape!	Ang iyong marka ay %d, ang pinakamataas na marka sa antas na ito ay %d. Subukan mo ulit!	Your score is %d, the highest score in this level is %d. Try again!	Makin ku shine %d, mafi girman maki a wannan matakin shine %d. Gwada kuma!	Dimegilio rẹ jẹ %d, Dimegilio ti o ga julọ ni ipele yii jẹ %d. Gbiyanju lẹẹkansi!	Сіздің ұпайыңыз %d, осы деңгейдегі ең жоғары ұпай – %d. Қайтадан байқап көріңіз!	Zure puntuazioa %d da, maila honetako puntuazio altuena %d da. Saiatu berriro!	Ang iyong marka ay %d, ang pinakamataas na marka sa antas na ito ay %d. Subukan muli!	A túa puntuación é %d, a puntuación máis alta neste nivel é %d. Téntao de novo!	Akara gị bụ %d, akara kachasị elu na ọkwa a bụ %d. Nwaa ọzọ!	Is é %d do scór, is é %d an scór is airde sa leibhéal seo. Bain triail eile as!	သင့်ရမှတ်မှာ %d ဖြစ်ပြီး၊ ဤအဆင့်တွင် အမြင့်ဆုံးရမှတ်မှာ %d ဖြစ်သည်။ ထပ်စမ်းကြည့်ပါ။	ຄະແນນຂອງທ່ານແມ່ນ %d, ຄະແນນສູງສຸດໃນລະດັບນີ້ແມ່ນ %d. ລອງອີກຄັ້ງ!	ពិន្ទុរបស់អ្នកគឺ %d ពិន្ទុខ្ពស់បំផុតក្នុងកម្រិតនេះគឺ %d។ ព្យាយាមម្តងទៀត!	귀하의 점수는 %d이고, 이 레벨의 최고 점수는 %d입니다. 다시 시도하세요!	သင့်ရမှတ်မှာ %d ဖြစ်ပြီး၊ ဤအဆင့်တွင် အမြင့်ဆုံးရမှတ်မှာ %d ဖြစ်သည်။ ထပ်စမ်းကြည့်ပါ။	
STR_GX_TETRIS_REPORT_RECORD	GAME	UNLIM	tetris	Congratulations! Your score is: %d. You have been the best of this level!	恭喜！您的分數是：%d。你已經是這個級別中最好的了！	恭喜！您的得分为：%d。您已是本关的佼佼者！	ยินดีด้วย! คะแนนของคุณคือ: %d คุณเป็นผู้ที่ดีที่สุดในด่านนี้!	¡Felicitaciones! Tu puntuación es: %d. ¡Has sido el mejor de este nivel!	Félicitations ! Votre score est de : %d. Vous avez été le meilleur de ce niveau !	Herzlichen Glückwunsch! Ihre Punktzahl beträgt: %d. Sie waren der Beste in diesem Level!	Поздравляем! Ваш счет: %d. Вы были лучшим на этом уровне!	Congratulazioni! Il tuo punteggio è: %d. Sei stato il migliore di questo livello!	مبروك! نتيجتك هي: %d. لقد كنت الأفضل في هذا المستوى!	Parabéns! A sua pontuação é: %d. Foste o melhor deste nível!	Tebrikler! Puanınız: %d. Bu seviyenin en iyisi oldunuz!	Xin chúc mừng! Điểm số của bạn là: %d. Bạn đã là người giỏi nhất trong cấp độ này!	Selamat! Skor Anda adalah: %d. Anda telah menjadi yang terbaik di level ini!	tahniah! Markah anda ialah: %d. Anda telah menjadi yang terbaik pada tahap ini!	बधाई हो! आपका स्कोर है: %d। आप इस लेवल में सबसे अच्छे रहे हैं!	Tillykke! Din score er: %d. Du har været den bedste på dette niveau!	Gratuluji! Vaše skóre je: %d. Byli jste nejlepší na této úrovni!	Gratulacje! Twój wynik to: %d. Byłeś najlepszy na tym poziomie!	Gratulálok! Az Ön pontszáma: %d. Te voltál a legjobb ezen a szinten!	Onnittelut! Sinun pisteesi on: %d. Olet ollut tämän tason paras!	Gratulerer! Poengsummen din er: %d. Du har vært den beste på dette nivået!	Gratulujem! Vaše skóre je: %d. Boli ste najlepší na tejto úrovni!	Gefeliciteerd! Je score is: %d. Je bent de beste van dit level!	Grattis! Din poäng är: %d. Du har varit bäst på den här nivån!	čestitamo! Vaš rezultat je: %d. Bili ste najbolji na ovoj razini!	Felicitări! Scorul tău este: %d. Ai fost cel mai bun de la acest nivel!	čestitke! Vaš rezultat je: %d. Bili ste najboljši na tej ravni!	Συγχαρητήρια! Η βαθμολογία σας είναι: %d. Ήσασταν ο καλύτερος αυτού του επιπέδου!	מזל טוב! הציון שלך הוא: %d. היית הכי טוב ברמה הזו!	честито! Вашият резултат е: %d. Ти беше най-добрият на това ниво!	अभिनंदन! तुमचा स्कोअर आहे: %d. तुम्ही या स्तरावर सर्वोत्तम आहात!	تبریک می گویم! امتیاز شما: %d است. تو بهترین این سطح بوده ای!	مبارک ہو! آپ کا سکور ہے: %d۔ آپ اس سطح کے بہترین رہے ہیں!	வாழ்த்துகள்! உங்கள் மதிப்பெண்: %d. நீங்கள் இந்த மட்டத்தில் சிறந்தவராக இருந்தீர்கள்!	অভিনন্দন! আপনার স্কোর হল: %d আপনি এই স্তরের সেরা হয়েছে!	ਵਧਾਈਆਂ! ਤੁਹਾਡਾ ਸਕੋਰ ਹੈ: %d। ਤੁਸੀਂ ਇਸ ਪੱਧਰ ਦੇ ਸਭ ਤੋਂ ਵਧੀਆ ਰਹੇ ਹੋ!	అభినందనలు! మీ స్కోర్: %d. మీరు ఈ స్థాయిలో అత్యుత్తమంగా ఉన్నారు!	Щиро вітаю! Ваш результат: %d. Ви були найкращими на цьому рівні!	અભિનંદન! તમારો સ્કોર છે: %d. તમે આ સ્તરના શ્રેષ્ઠ રહ્યા છો!	ಅಭಿನಂದನೆಗಳು! ನಿಮ್ಮ ಸ್ಕೋರ್: %d. ನೀವು ಈ ಮಟ್ಟದಲ್ಲಿ ಅತ್ಯುತ್ತಮವಾಗಿದ್ದೀರಿ!	Siyakuhalalisela! Isikolo sakho sithi: %d. Ubengcono kakhulu kuleli zinga!	Sivuyisana nawe! Inqaku lakho ngu: %d. Ube ngoyena ubalaseleyo kweli nqanaba!	Hongera! Alama yako ni: %d. Umekuwa bora zaidi wa kiwango hiki!	Baie geluk! Jou telling is: %d. Jy was die beste van hierdie vlak!	Sveikiname! Jūsų rezultatas: %d. Jūs buvote geriausias šiame lygyje!	Apsveicam! Jūsu rezultāts ir: %d. Jūs esat bijis labākais šajā līmenī!	Palju õnne! Sinu tulemus on: %d. Olete olnud selle taseme parim!	Շնորհավորում եմ: Ձեր գնահատականն է՝ %d: Դուք այս մակարդակի լավագույնն եք եղել:	გილოცავ! თქვენი ქულაა: %d. თქვენ ამ დონის საუკეთესო იყავით!	Felicitări! Scorul tău este: %d. Ai fost cel mai bun de la acest nivel!	അഭിനന്ദനങ്ങൾ! നിങ്ങളുടെ സ്കോർ: %d. നിങ്ങൾ ഈ ലെവലിലെ ഏറ്റവും മികച്ച ആളായിരുന്നു!	ଅଭିନନ୍ଦନ! ଆପଣଙ୍କର ସ୍କୋର ହେଉଛି:% d ତୁମେ ଏହି ସ୍ତରର ଶ୍ରେଷ୍ଠ ହୋଇଛ!	urime! Rezultati juaj është: %d. Ju keni qenë më të mirët e këtij niveli!	অভিনন্দন! আপোনাৰ স্ক'ৰ হ'ল: %d। এই স্তৰৰ আপুনি শ্ৰেষ্ঠ হৈ আহিছে!	Təbrik edirik! Hesabınız: %d. Siz bu səviyyənin ən yaxşısı olmusunuz!	恭喜你！	Felicitats! La teva puntuació és: %d. Has estat el millor d'aquest nivell!	Félicitations! Votre score est : %d. Vous avez été le meilleur à ce niveau-là !	Til hamingju! Einkunnin þín er: %d. Þú hefur verið bestur á þessu stigi!	¡Felicitaciones! Tu puntuación es: %d. ¡Has sido el mejor de este nivel!	Секоја чест! Вашиот резултат е: %d. Вие сте биле најдобри на ова ниво!	Parabéns! Sua pontuação é: %d. Você foi o melhor deste nível!	Честитамо! Ваш резултат је: %д. Били сте најбољи на овом нивоу!	Kea u babatsa! Lintlha tsa hau ke: %d. U bile ea molemo ka ho fetisisa boemong bona!	Mga papuri! Ang iyong marka ay: %d. Ikaw ang pinakamagaling sa antas na ito!	Congratulations! Your score is: %d. You have been the best of this level!	Taya murna! Makin ku shine: %d. Kun kasance mafi kyawun wannan matakin!	Oriire! Dimegilio rẹ jẹ: %d. O ti dara julọ ni ipele yii!	Құттықтаймыз! Сіздің ұпайыңыз: %d. Сіз осы деңгейдегі ең жақсы болдыңыз!	Zorionak! Zure puntuazioa hau da: %d. Maila honetako onena izan zara!	Binabati kita! Ang iyong marka ay: %d. Ikaw ang naging pinakamahusay sa antas na ito!	Parabéns! A túa puntuación é: %d. Fuches o mellor deste nivel!	Ekele! Akara gị bụ: %d. Ị bụ onye kacha mma na ọkwa a!	Comhghairdeachas! Is é do scór: %d. Bhí tú an ceann is fearr ar an leibhéal seo!	ဂုဏ်ယူပါသည်။ သင့်ရမှတ်မှာ %d။ သင်သည် ဤအဆင့်၏ အကောင်းဆုံးဖြစ်ခဲ့သည်။	ຊົມເຊີຍ! ຄະແນນຂອງທ່ານແມ່ນ: %d. ເຈົ້າໄດ້ດີທີ່ສຸດໃນລະດັບນີ້!	អបអរសាទរ! ពិន្ទុរបស់អ្នកគឺ៖ %d ។ អ្នកបានល្អបំផុតក្នុងកម្រិតនេះ!	축하합니다! 귀하의 점수는 %d입니다. 이 레벨에서 최고였습니다!	ဂုဏ်ယူပါသည်။ သင့်ရမှတ်မှာ %d။ သင်သည် ဤအဆင့်၏ အကောင်းဆုံးဖြစ်ခဲ့သည်။	
STR_GX_TETRIS_PASS	GAME	UNLIM	tetris	Good! You have passed this level. Your current score is: %d. Would you like to enter the next level?	好的！你已經通過了這個級別。您目前的分數是：%d。您想進入下一個級別嗎？	很好！您已通过本关。您目前的得分为：%d。您想进入下一关吗？	ดีมาก! คุณผ่านด่านนี้แล้ว คะแนนปัจจุบันของคุณคือ: %d คุณต้องการเข้าสู่ด่านต่อไปหรือไม่	¡Bien! Has superado este nivel. Tu puntuación actual es: %d. ¿Te gustaría pasar al siguiente nivel?	Bien ! Vous avez réussi ce niveau. Votre score actuel est de : %d. Souhaitez-vous passer au niveau suivant ?	Gut! Sie haben dieses Level geschafft. Ihre aktuelle Punktzahl beträgt: %d. Möchten Sie das nächste Level erreichen?	Хорошо! Вы прошли этот уровень. Ваш текущий счет: %d. Хотите перейти на следующий уровень?	Bene! Hai superato questo livello. Il tuo punteggio attuale è: %d. Vuoi entrare nel livello successivo?	جيد! لقد اجتزت هذا المستوى. نتيجتك الحالية هي: %d. هل ترغب في الدخول إلى المستوى التالي؟	Bom! Passou deste nível. A sua pontuação atual é: %d. Gostaria de entrar no próximo nível?	İyi! Bu seviyeyi geçtiniz. Mevcut puanınız: %d. Bir sonraki seviyeye geçmek ister misiniz?	Tốt! Bạn đã vượt qua cấp độ này. Điểm số hiện tại của bạn là: %d. Bạn có muốn vào cấp độ tiếp theo không?	Bagus! Anda telah melewati level ini. Skor Anda saat ini adalah: %d. Apakah Anda ingin memasuki level berikutnya?	Bagus! Anda telah melepasi tahap ini. Markah semasa anda ialah: %d. Adakah anda ingin memasuki peringkat seterusnya?	अच्छा! आपने यह लेवल पास कर लिया है। आपका मौजूदा स्कोर है: %d। क्या आप अगले लेवल में प्रवेश करना चाहेंगे?	God! Du har bestået dette niveau. Din nuværende score er: %d. Vil du ind på næste niveau?	Dobrý! Tuto úroveň jste překonali. Vaše aktuální skóre je: %d. Chtěli byste vstoupit do další úrovně?	Świetnie! Zdałeś ten poziom. Twój obecny wynik to: %d. Czy chcesz przejść do następnego poziomu?	Jó! Ön túllépte ezt a szintet. Jelenlegi pontszámod: %d. Szeretnél a következő szintre lépni?	Hyvä! Olet läpäissyt tämän tason. Nykyinen pisteesi on: %d. Haluatko siirtyä seuraavalle tasolle?	God! Du har passert dette nivået. Din nåværende poengsum er: %d. Vil du gå inn på neste nivå?	Dobre! Prešli ste touto úrovňou. Vaše aktuálne skóre je: %d. Chceli by ste vstúpiť do ďalšej úrovne?	Goed! Je hebt dit level gehaald. Je huidige score is: %d. Wil je naar het volgende level?	Bra! Du har klarat denna nivå. Din nuvarande poäng är: %d. Vill du gå in på nästa nivå?	Dobro! Prošli ste ovu razinu. Vaš trenutni rezultat je: %d. Želite li prijeći na sljedeću razinu?	Bun! Ai trecut de acest nivel. Scorul dvs. actual este: %d. Vrei să intri în următorul nivel?	Dobro! To raven ste opravili. Vaš trenutni rezultat je: %d. Bi radi vstopili na naslednjo stopnjo?	Καλός! Έχετε περάσει αυτό το επίπεδο. Η τρέχουσα βαθμολογία σας είναι: %d. Θα θέλατε να μπείτε στο επόμενο επίπεδο;	טוֹב! עברת את הרמה הזו. הציון הנוכחי שלך הוא: %d. האם תרצה להיכנס לשלב הבא?	добре! Вие сте преминали това ниво. Текущият ви резултат е: %d. Искате ли да влезете в следващото ниво?	छान! तुम्ही ही पातळी पार केली आहे. तुमचा सध्याचा स्कोअर आहे: %d. आपण पुढील स्तरावर प्रवेश करू इच्छिता?	خوب! شما این سطح را پشت سر گذاشته اید. امتیاز فعلی شما: %d است. آیا می خواهید وارد مرحله بعدی شوید؟	اچھا! آپ اس درجے کو پاس کر چکے ہیں۔ آپ کا موجودہ سکور ہے: %d۔ کیا آپ اگلے درجے میں داخل ہونا چاہیں گے؟	நல்லது! நீங்கள் இந்த நிலையை கடந்துவிட்டீர்கள். உங்கள் தற்போதைய மதிப்பெண்: %d. அடுத்த நிலைக்குச் செல்ல விரும்புகிறீர்களா?	ভালো! আপনি এই স্তর পাস করেছেন। আপনার বর্তমান স্কোর হল: %d আপনি কি পরবর্তী স্তরে প্রবেশ করতে চান?	ਅੱਛਾ! ਤੁਸੀਂ ਇਸ ਪੱਧਰ ਨੂੰ ਪਾਸ ਕਰ ਲਿਆ ਹੈ। ਤੁਹਾਡਾ ਮੌਜੂਦਾ ਸਕੋਰ ਹੈ: %d। ਕੀ ਤੁਸੀਂ ਅਗਲੇ ਪੱਧਰ ਵਿੱਚ ਦਾਖਲ ਹੋਣਾ ਚਾਹੋਗੇ?	బాగుంది! మీరు ఈ స్థాయిని దాటిపోయారు. మీ ప్రస్తుత స్కోర్: %d. మీరు తదుపరి స్థాయికి ప్రవేశించాలనుకుంటున్నారా?	добре! Ви пройшли цей рівень. Ваш поточний результат: %d. Чи хотіли б ви перейти на наступний рівень?	સારું! તમે આ સ્તરને પાર કરી લીધું છે. તમારો વર્તમાન સ્કોર છે: %d. શું તમે આગલા સ્તરમાં પ્રવેશવા માંગો છો?	ಒಳ್ಳೆಯದು! ನೀವು ಈ ಹಂತವನ್ನು ದಾಟಿದ್ದೀರಿ. ನಿಮ್ಮ ಪ್ರಸ್ತುತ ಸ್ಕೋರ್: %d. ನೀವು ಮುಂದಿನ ಹಂತವನ್ನು ಪ್ರವೇಶಿಸಲು ಬಯಸುವಿರಾ?	Kuhle! Udlule kuleli zinga. Isikolo sakho samanje sithi: %d. Ungathanda ukungena ileveli elandelayo?	Kulungile! Udlule kweli nqanaba. Inqaku lakho langoku ngu: %d. Ngaba ungathanda ukungena kwinqanaba elilandelayo?	Nzuri! Umepita kiwango hiki. Alama yako ya sasa ni: %d. Je, ungependa kuingia kiwango kinachofuata?	Goed! Jy het hierdie vlak geslaag. Jou huidige telling is: %d. Wil jy die volgende vlak betree?	Gerai! Jūs įveikėte šį lygį. Jūsų dabartinis rezultatas yra: %d. Ar norėtumėte patekti į kitą lygį?	Labi! Jūs esat izturējis šo līmeni. Jūsu pašreizējais rezultāts ir: %d. Vai vēlaties pāriet uz nākamo līmeni?	Hea! Olete selle taseme läbinud. Sinu praegune tulemus on: %d. Kas soovite siseneda järgmisele tasemele?	Լավ! Դուք անցել եք այս մակարդակը։ Ձեր ընթացիկ միավորն է՝ %d: Կցանկանայի՞ք մտնել հաջորդ մակարդակ:	კარგი! თქვენ გაიარეთ ეს დონე. თქვენი ამჟამინდელი ქულაა: %d. გსურთ შეხვიდეთ შემდეგ ეტაპზე?	Bun! Ai trecut de acest nivel. Scorul dvs. actual este: %d. Vrei să intri în următorul nivel?	നല്ലത്! നിങ്ങൾ ഈ ലെവൽ കഴിഞ്ഞു. നിങ്ങളുടെ നിലവിലെ സ്കോർ: %d. അടുത്ത ലെവലിൽ പ്രവേശിക്കാൻ നിങ്ങൾ ആഗ്രഹിക്കുന്നുണ്ടോ?	ଭଲ! ଆପଣ ଏହି ସ୍ତର ଅତିକ୍ରମ କରିଛନ୍ତି | ତୁମର ସାମ୍ପ୍ରତିକ ସ୍କୋର ହେଉଛି:% d ଆପଣ ପରବର୍ତ୍ତୀ ସ୍ତରକୁ ପ୍ରବେଶ କରିବାକୁ ଚାହୁଁଛନ୍ତି କି?	Mirë! Ju e keni kaluar këtë nivel. Rezultati juaj aktual është: %d. Dëshironi të hyni në nivelin tjetër?	ভাল! আপুনি এই স্তৰত উত্তীৰ্ণ হৈছে। আপোনাৰ বৰ্তমানৰ নম্বৰ হৈছে: %d । আপুনি পৰৱৰ্তী স্তৰত প্ৰৱেশ কৰিব বিচাৰেনে?	Yaxşı! Siz bu səviyyəni keçmisiniz. Cari xalınız: %d. Növbəti səviyyəyə daxil olmaq istərdinizmi?	好！你已經通過咗呢個級別。你而家嘅分數係： % 啲。	Bé! Has superat aquest nivell. La teva puntuació actual és: %d. T'agradaria entrar al següent nivell?	Bien! Vous avez dépassé ce niveau. Votre pointage actuel est : %d. Voulez-vous passer au prochain niveau ?	Gott! Þú hefur staðist þetta stig. Núverandi stig þitt er: %d. Viltu fara á næsta stig?	¡Bien! Has superado este nivel. Tu puntuación actual es: %d. ¿Te gustaría pasar al siguiente nivel?	Добро! Го поминавте ова ниво. Вашиот моментален резултат е: %d. Дали сакате да влезете на следното ниво?	Ótimo! Você passou deste nível. Sua pontuação atual é: %d. Você gostaria de entrar no próximo nível?	Добро! Прешли сте овај ниво. Ваш тренутни резултат је: %д. Да ли бисте желели да уђете у следећи ниво?	Ho lokile! O fetile boemong bona. Lintlha tsa hau tsa hajoale ke: %d. O ka thabela ho kena boemong bo latelang?	Magaling! Nalampasan mo na ang antas na ito. Ang iyong kasalukuyang marka ay: %d. Gusto mo bang pumasok sa susunod na antas?	Good! You have passed this level. Your current score is: %d. Would you like to enter the next level?	Yayi kyau! Kun wuce wannan matakin. Makin ku na yanzu shine: %d. Kuna so ku shiga mataki na gaba?	O dara! O ti kọja ipele yii. Dimegilio lọwọlọwọ rẹ jẹ: %d. Ṣe o fẹ lati tẹ ipele ti o tẹle?	Жақсы! Сіз бұл деңгейден өттіңіз. Ағымдағы ұпайыңыз: %d. Келесі деңгейге өткіңіз келе ме?	Ona! Maila hau gainditu duzu. Zure uneko puntuazioa hau da: %d. Hurrengo mailan sartu nahiko zenuke?	Magaling! Nalampasan mo na ang antas na ito. Ang iyong kasalukuyang marka ay: %d. Gusto mo bang pumasok sa susunod na antas?	Ben! Pasaches este nivel. A túa puntuación actual é: %d. Gustaríache entrar no seguinte nivel?	Ọ dị mma! Ị gafere ọkwa a. Akara gị ugbu a bụ: %d. Ọ ga-amasị gị ịbanye n'ọkwa na-esote?	Maith sibh! D'éirigh leat an leibhéal seo. Is é do scór reatha: %d. Ar mhaith leat dul isteach sa chéad leibhéal eile?	ကောင်းတယ်! မင်း ဒီအဆင့်ကို ကျော်သွားပြီ။ သင်၏ လက်ရှိရမှတ်မှာ %d။ နောက်တစ်ဆင့်တက်လိုပါသလား။	ດີ! ທ່ານ​ໄດ້​ຜ່ານ​ລະ​ດັບ​ນີ້​. ຄະແນນປັດຈຸບັນຂອງທ່ານແມ່ນ: %d. ທ່ານຕ້ອງການເຂົ້າສູ່ລະດັບຕໍ່ໄປບໍ?	ល្អ! អ្នកបានឆ្លងកាត់កម្រិតនេះ។ ពិន្ទុបច្ចុប្បន្នរបស់អ្នកគឺ៖ %d ។ តើអ្នកចង់ចូលកម្រិតបន្ទាប់ទេ?	좋습니다! 이 레벨을 통과했습니다. 현재 점수는 %d입니다. 다음 레벨로 이동하시겠습니까?	ကောင်းတယ်! မင်း ဒီအဆင့်ကို ကျော်သွားပြီ။ သင်၏ လက်ရှိရမှတ်မှာ %d။ နောက်တစ်ဆင့်တက်လိုပါသလား။	
STR_GX_TETRIS_PASS_LAST	GAME	UNLIM	tetris	Superb! You have passed the highest level of this game, you score is: %d. Nothing is impossible for a willing heart!	高超！您已經通過了本遊戲的最高級別，您的得分是：%d。只要有心，沒有什麼是不可能的！	棒极了！您已通过本游戏的最高关，您的得分为：%d。只要有心，没有什么是不可能的！	ยอดเยี่ยม! คุณผ่านด่านสูงสุดของเกมนี้แล้ว คะแนนของคุณคือ: %d ไม่มีอะไรที่เป็นไปไม่ได้สำหรับหัวใจที่เต็มใจ!	¡Excelente! Has superado el nivel más alto de este juego, tu puntuación es: %d. ¡Nada es imposible para un corazón dispuesto!	Super ! Vous avez réussi le niveau le plus élevé de ce jeu, votre score est de : %d. Rien n'est impossible à un cœur bien disposé !	Hervorragend! Sie haben das höchste Level dieses Spiels geschafft, Ihre Punktzahl beträgt: %d. Für ein williges Herz ist nichts unmöglich!	Превосходно! Вы прошли наивысший уровень этой игры, ваш счет: %d. Нет ничего невозможного для готового сердца!	Superbo! Hai superato il livello più alto di questo gioco, il tuo punteggio è: %d. Niente è impossibile per un cuore disposto!	رائع! لقد اجتزت أعلى مستوى في هذه اللعبة، نتيجتك هي: %d. لا شيء مستحيل بالنسبة للقلب المستعد!	Excelente! Passou o nível mais alto deste jogo, a sua pontuação é: %d. Nada é impossível para um coração disposto!	Harika! Bu oyunun en yüksek seviyesini geçtiniz, puanınız: %d. İstekli bir kalp için hiçbir şey imkansız değildir!	Tuyệt vời! Bạn đã vượt qua cấp độ cao nhất của trò chơi này, điểm số của bạn là: %d. Không có gì là không thể đối với một trái tim sẵn sàng!	Luar biasa! Anda telah melewati level tertinggi permainan ini, skor Anda adalah: %d. Tidak ada yang mustahil bagi hati yang bersedia!	Hebat! Anda telah melepasi tahap tertinggi permainan ini, markah anda ialah: %d. Tiada yang mustahil untuk hati yang rela!	शानदार! आपने इस गेम का सबसे ज़्यादा स्कोर पास कर लिया है, आपका स्कोर है: %d। एक इच्छुक दिल के लिए कुछ भी असंभव नहीं है!	Fantastisk! Du har bestået det højeste niveau i dette spil, din score er: %d. Intet er umuligt for et villigt hjerte!	Nádherný! Prošli jste nejvyšší úrovní této hry, vaše skóre je: %d. Pro ochotné srdce není nic nemožné!	Wspaniale! Zdałeś najwyższy poziom tej gry, twój wynik to: %d. Dla chętnego serca nie ma rzeczy niemożliwych!	Nagyszerű! Elérted a játék legmagasabb szintjét, a pontszámod: %d. Egy készséges szívnek semmi sem lehetetlen!	Loistavaa! Olet läpäissyt tämän pelin korkeimman tason, pisteesi on: %d. Mikään ei ole mahdotonta halukkaalle sydämelle!	Fantastisk! Du har bestått det høyeste nivået i dette spillet, poengsummen er: %d. Ingenting er umulig for et villig hjerte!	Skvelé! Prešli ste najvyššou úrovňou tejto hry, vaše skóre je: %d. Pre ochotné srdce nie je nič nemožné!	Fantastisch! Je hebt het hoogste level van dit spel gehaald, je score is: %d. Niets is onmogelijk voor een bereidwillig hart!	Superb! Du har klarat den högsta nivån i detta spel, din poäng är: %d. Ingenting är omöjligt för ett villigt hjärta!	vrhunsko! Prošli ste najvišu razinu ove igre, vaš rezultat je: %d. Voljnom srcu ništa nije nemoguće!	Superb! Ați depășit cel mai înalt nivel al acestui joc, scorul este: %d. Nimic nu este imposibil pentru o inimă dispusă!	vrhunsko! Presegli ste najvišjo raven te igre, vaš rezultat je: %d. Nič ni nemogoče za voljno srce!	Υπέροχος! Έχετε περάσει το υψηλότερο επίπεδο αυτού του παιχνιδιού, σκοράρετε είναι: %d. Τίποτα δεν είναι αδύνατο για μια πρόθυμη καρδιά!	מְצוּיָן! עברת את הרמה הגבוהה ביותר של המשחק הזה, הציון שלך הוא: %d. שום דבר אינו בלתי אפשרי עבור לב מוכן!	страхотно! Преминахте най-високото ниво на тази игра, резултатът ви е: %d. Няма невъзможни неща за желаещото сърце!	उत्कृष्ट! तुम्ही या गेमची सर्वोच्च पातळी पार केली आहे, तुमचा स्कोअर आहे: %d. इच्छुक हृदयासाठी काहीही अशक्य नाही!	فوق العاده! شما بالاترین سطح این بازی را پشت سر گذاشته اید، امتیاز شما این است: %d. هیچ چیز برای یک قلب مشتاق غیر ممکن نیست!	شاندار! آپ اس گیم کی اعلیٰ ترین سطح سے گزر چکے ہیں، آپ کا اسکور ہے: %d۔ آمادہ دل کے لیے کچھ بھی ناممکن نہیں!	சூப்பர்! இந்த விளையாட்டின் மிக உயர்ந்த நிலையை நீங்கள் கடந்துவிட்டீர்கள், நீங்கள் பெற்ற மதிப்பெண்: %d. விருப்பமுள்ள இதயத்தால் முடியாதது எதுவுமில்லை!	চমত্কার! আপনি এই গেমের সর্বোচ্চ স্তর অতিক্রম করেছেন, আপনার স্কোর হল: %d। ইচ্ছুক হৃদয়ের পক্ষে কিছুই অসম্ভব নয়!	ਸ਼ਾਨਦਾਰ! ਤੁਸੀਂ ਇਸ ਗੇਮ ਦਾ ਸਭ ਤੋਂ ਉੱਚਾ ਪੱਧਰ ਪਾਸ ਕਰ ਲਿਆ ਹੈ, ਤੁਹਾਡਾ ਸਕੋਰ ਹੈ: %d। ਚਾਹਵਾਨ ਦਿਲ ਲਈ ਕੁਝ ਵੀ ਅਸੰਭਵ ਨਹੀਂ ਹੈ!	అద్భుతం! మీరు ఈ గేమ్‌లో అత్యధిక స్థాయిని అధిగమించారు, మీ స్కోర్: %d. ఇష్టపడే హృదయానికి అసాధ్యమైనది ఏదీ లేదు!	Чудово! Ви пройшли найвищий рівень цієї гри, ваш результат: %d. Для охочого серця немає нічого неможливого!	શાનદાર! તમે આ રમતનું સર્વોચ્ચ સ્તર પસાર કર્યું છે, તમારો સ્કોર છે: %d. ઈચ્છુક હૃદય માટે કશું જ અશક્ય નથી!	ಅದ್ಭುತ! ನೀವು ಈ ಆಟದ ಅತ್ಯುನ್ನತ ಮಟ್ಟವನ್ನು ದಾಟಿದ್ದೀರಿ, ನಿಮ್ಮ ಸ್ಕೋರ್: %d. ಸಿದ್ಧಮನಸ್ಸಿಗೆ ಯಾವುದೂ ಅಸಾಧ್ಯವಲ್ಲ!	Kuhle kakhulu! Uphumelele izinga eliphezulu kakhulu lalo mdlalo, uthole amaphuzu: %d. Akukho okungenzeki ngenhliziyo evumayo!	Umhle kakhulu! Uphumelele elona nqanaba liphezulu lalo mdlalo, ufumana amanqaku: %d. Akukho nto ingenakwenzeka kwintliziyo evumayo!	Bora! Umepita kiwango cha juu zaidi cha mchezo huu, alama ni: %d. Hakuna lisilowezekana kwa moyo ulio tayari!	Fantasties! Jy het die hoogste vlak van hierdie speletjie geslaag, jou telling is: %d. Niks is onmoontlik vir 'n gewillige hart nie!	Nuostabu! Įveikėte aukščiausią šio žaidimo lygį, jūsų rezultatas yra: %d. Nieko nėra neįmanomo noriai širdžiai!	Lieliski! Jūs esat izturējis šīs spēles augstāko līmeni, jūsu rezultāts ir: %d. Labprātīgai sirdij nekas nav neiespējams!	Suurepärane! Olete läbinud selle mängu kõrgeima taseme, teie tulemus on: %d. Algavale südamele pole miski võimatu!	Հոյակապ Դուք անցել եք այս խաղի ամենաբարձր մակարդակը, ձեր հաշիվը կազմում է՝ %d: Կամավոր սրտի համար անհնարին ոչինչ չկա:	შესანიშნავი! თქვენ გაიარეთ ამ თამაშის უმაღლესი დონე, თქვენ ქულა: %d. მსურველი გულისთვის შეუძლებელი არაფერია!	Superb! Ați depășit cel mai înalt nivel al acestui joc, scorul este: %d. Nimic nu este imposibil pentru o inimă dispusă!	ഗംഭീരം! നിങ്ങൾ ഈ ഗെയിമിൻ്റെ ഉയർന്ന ലെവൽ പാസായി, നിങ്ങളുടെ സ്കോർ: %d. മനസ്സൊരുക്കമുള്ള ഹൃദയത്തിന് അസാധ്യമായി ഒന്നുമില്ല!	ଉତ୍ତମ! ଆପଣ ଏହି ଖେଳର ସର୍ବୋଚ୍ଚ ସ୍ତର ଅତିକ୍ରମ କରିଛନ୍ତି, ଆପଣ ସ୍କୋର କରୁଛନ୍ତି:% d | ଇଚ୍ଛୁକ ହୃଦୟ ପାଇଁ କିଛି ଅସମ୍ଭବ ନୁହେଁ!	E shkëlqyeshme! Ju keni kaluar nivelin më të lartë të kësaj loje, ju shënoni është: %d. Asgjë nuk është e pamundur për një zemër të gatshme!	চমৎকাৰ! আপুনি এই খেলৰ সৰ্বোচ্চ স্তৰ উত্তীৰ্ণ হৈছে, আপুনি স্ক'ৰ হ'ল: %d। ইচ্ছুক হৃদয়ৰ বাবে একোৱেই অসম্ভৱ নহয়!	Əla! Siz bu oyunun ən yüksək səviyyəsini keçmisiniz, xal qazandınız: %d. İstəkli bir ürək üçün mümkünsüz heç nə yoxdur!	超級好！你已經通過咗呢個遊戲嘅最高水平，你嘅分數係： % 啲。	Genial! Has superat el nivell més alt d'aquest joc, la teva puntuació és: %d. Res és impossible per a un cor disposat!	Super! Vous avez réussi le niveau le plus élevé de ce jeu, votre score est : %d. Rien n'est impossible à un cœur bien disposé !	Frábært! Þú hefur staðist hæsta stig þessa leiks, þú skorar: %d. Ekkert er ómögulegt fyrir fúst hjarta!	¡Excelente! Has superado el nivel más alto de este juego, tu puntuación es: %d. ¡Nada es imposible para un corazón dispuesto!	Одлично! Го поминавте највисокото ниво на оваа игра, резултатот е: %d. Ништо не е невозможно за доброволно срце!	Ótimo! Você passou do nível mais alto deste jogo, sua pontuação é: %d. Nada é impossível para um coração disposto!	Суперб! Прешли сте највиши ниво ове игре, ваш резултат је: %д. Ништа није немогуће за вољно срце!	E ntle haholo! U fetile boemo bo holimo ka ho fetisisa papaling ena, u fumane lintlha tse latelang: %d. Ha ho letho le ke keng la khoneha bakeng sa pelo e ratang!	Napakagaling! Nakapasa ka na sa pinakamataas na antas ng larong ito, ang iyong puntos ay: %d. Walang imposible para sa isang handang puso!	Superb! You have passed the highest level of this game, you score is: %d. Nothing is impossible for a willing heart!	Kyakkyawan! Kun wuce matakin mafi girman wannan wasan, maki shine: %d. Babu wani abu da ya gagara ga mai son zuciya!	Dara julọ! O ti kọja ipele ti o ga julọ ti ere yii, o jẹ Dimegilio: %d. Ko si ohun ti ko ṣee ṣe fun ọkan ti o fẹ!	Керемет! Сіз осы ойынның ең жоғары деңгейінен өттіңіз, ұпайыңыз: %d. Ерікті жүрек үшін мүмкін емес ештеңе жоқ!	Ikaragarria! Joko honen maila gorena gainditu duzu, puntuazioa hau da: %d. Ezer ez da ezinezkoa bihotz gogotsu batentzat!	Napakahusay! Nalampasan mo ang pinakamataas na antas ng larong ito, ang iyong iskor ay: %d. Walang imposible para sa isang kusang puso!	¡Excelente! Pasaches o nivel máis alto deste xogo, a túa puntuación é: %d. Nada é imposible para un corazón disposto!	magburu onwe ya! Ị gafere ọkwa kachasị elu nke egwuregwu a, akara gị bụ: %d. Ọ dịghị ihe na-agaghị ekwe omume maka obi njikere!	Ar fheabhas! D'éirigh leat sa leibhéal is airde den chluiche seo, is é an scór tú: %d. Ní dhéanfaidh aon ní dodhéanta do chroí toilteanach!	အရမ်းကောင်းတယ်။ သင်သည် ဤဂိမ်း၏ အမြင့်ဆုံးအဆင့်ကို အောင်မြင်ပြီးပြီ၊ သင်ရမှတ်မှာ %d ဖြစ်သည်။ စေတနာစိတ်ရှိဖို့ ဘယ်အရာမှ မဖြစ်နိုင်ပါဘူး။	ສຸດຍອດ! ທ່ານ​ໄດ້​ຜ່ານ​ລະ​ດັບ​ສູງ​ສຸດ​ຂອງ​ເກມ​ນີ້​, ທ່ານ​ໄດ້​ຄະ​ແນນ​: %d​. ບໍ່ມີຫຍັງເປັນໄປບໍ່ໄດ້ສໍາລັບຫົວໃຈທີ່ເຕັມໃຈ!	អស្ចារ្យ! អ្នកបានឆ្លងផុតកម្រិតខ្ពស់បំផុតនៃហ្គេមនេះ អ្នកទទួលបានពិន្ទុ៖ %d ។ គ្មាន​អ្វី​ដែល​មិន​អាច​ទៅ​រួច​សម្រាប់​ចិត្ត​ស្មោះ​!	훌륭합니다! 이 게임의 최고 레벨을 통과했습니다. 귀하의 점수는 %d입니다. 기꺼이 노력하는 사람에게는 불가능한 것이 없습니다!	အရမ်းကောင်းတယ်။ သင်သည် ဤဂိမ်း၏ အမြင့်ဆုံးအဆင့်ကို အောင်မြင်ပြီးပြီ၊ သင်ရမှတ်မှာ %d ဖြစ်သည်။ စေတနာစိတ်ရှိဖို့ ဘယ်အရာမှ မဖြစ်နိုင်ပါဘူး။	
STR_GX_TETRIS_HERO_LEVEL	GAME	UNLIM	tetris	Level	等級	关卡	ระดับ	Nivel	Niveau	Level	Уровень	Livello	المستوى	Nível	Seviye	Cấp độ	Level	Tahap	लेवल	Niveau	Úroveň	Poziom	Szint	Taso	Nivå	úroveň	Level	Nivå	Razina	Nivel	Raven	Επίπεδο	רָמָה	Ниво	पातळी	سطح	سطح	நிலை	স্তর	ਪੱਧਰ	స్థాయి	Рівень	સ્તર	ಮಟ್ಟ	Izinga	Inqanaba	Kiwango	Vlak	Lygis	Līmenis	Tase	Մակարդակ	დონე	Nivel	ലെവൽ	ସ୍ତର	Niveli	স্তৰ	Səviyyə	級數	Nivell	Niveau	Stig	Nivel	Ниво	Nível	Ниво	Boemo	antas	Level	Mataki	Ipele	Деңгей	Maila	Antas	Nivel	Ọkwa	Leibhéal	အဆင့်	ລະດັບ	កម្រិត	레벨	အဆင့်	
STR_GX_TETRIS_HERO_SCORE	GAME	UNLIM	tetris	Score	分數	得分	คะแนน	Puntuación	Score	Punktzahl	Очки	Punteggio	النتيجة	Pontuação	Puan	Điểm số	Skor	Skor	स्कोर	Score	Skóre	Wynik	Pontszám	Pisteet	Score	skóre	Score	Göra	Postići	Scor	rezultat	Σκορ	צִיוּן	резултат	स्कोअर	امتیاز	سکور	மதிப்பெண்	স্কোর	ਸਕੋਰ	స్కోర్	Оцінка	સ્કોર	ಸ್ಕೋರ್	Umphumela	Inqaku	Alama	Telling	Rezultatas	Rezultāts	Skoor	Միավոր	ქულა	Scor	സ്കോർ	ସ୍କୋର |	Rezultati	মানংক	Hesab	分數	Puntuació	Note	Skora	Puntuación	Резултат	Pontuação	Резултат	Laduma	Puntos	Score	Ci	O wole	Ұпай	Puntuazioa	Puntos	Puntuación	Akara	Scór	နိုင်ပြီ	ຄະແນນ	ពិន្ទុ	점수	နိုင်ပြီ	
##number	11
